welcome to category five technology TV
カテゴリ5テクノロジーテレビへようこそ
tonight we've got some great products
今夜私たちはいくつかの素晴らしい製品を持っています
we're gonna be looking at first of all
私たちはまず最初 に見ているつもりです
I'm so smooth so I want a really good
私はとても滑らかだ から私は本当に良いものが欲しい
night's sleep tonight I'm gonna do it
今夜の夜の睡眠私は それをやるつもりです
with a really cool mask that is going to
に起こっている 本当にクールなマスクと
help me sleep get rid of all tinnitus
私が眠るのを手伝って すべての耳鳴りを取り除きます
symptoms by giving me a audio invite
音声による招待 を受けて症状が 出る
home stereo oh you just got to see it
ホームステレオあああなたはちょうどそれを見ることができました
it's cheap it's affordable it's great
それは安いです それは手頃な価格ですそれは素晴らしいです
and we've got an Android TV stick
Android TVスティックがあります
yes it's gonna replace our amazon firetv
はいそれは私達のアマゾンfiretvを取り替えるつもりです
stick and even our Raspberry Pi 3
スティックと私たちのラズベリーパイ3
connected to the terminal music and our
ターミナルミュージックと私たちの
Roku stick they they do make yeah you
Roku stick 彼らは彼らをやっているよ
have one of those yeah it's gonna
それらの 1つを持っている
replace that yeah nice we're gonna be
それを交換してください
looking at an Android device that you
あなたがその Android デバイスを 見ている
plug into your TV
テレビに接続する
it's got exceptional Wi-Fi it plays
それはそれが再生する優れたWi-Fiを持っています
YouTube videos seamlessly in Full HD and
フルHDでのシームレスなYouTubeの動画や
even up to 4k you don't want to miss
見逃したくない4kまで
this sticker rack this is category 5
この ステッカーラックこれ はカテゴリー 5です
technology TV
テクノロジーテレビ
[Music]
[音楽]
our live recordings are trusted only to
私たちのライブ録音だけ に 、信頼されています
solid-state drives by Kingston
キングストンによるソリッドステートドライブ
technology revive your computer with
技術はあなたのコンピュータを復活させます
improved performance and reliability
性能と 信頼性の向上
over traditional hard drives with
従来のハードドライブに
Kingston SSDs category 5 TV streams live
Kingston SSDの カテゴリ5 TVストリームがライブ
with Telestream Wirecast and nimble
Telestream Wirecastで軽快に
streamer tune in every week on roku Kodi
roku Kodi での毎週ストリーマ曲
Plex and other HLS video players for
プレックスや その他のHLSビデオプレーヤー
local show times visit category 5 TV
ローカルショーの時間はカテゴリ5を訪問
category 5 TV is a member of the tech
category 5 TVはtechのメンバーです
podcast network if it's tech it's here
Podcast ネットワークが ハイテク なら ここ
cat 5 TV slash TPN and the international
猫5テレビスラッシュTPNと 国際
association of internet broadcasters cat
インターネット放送局協会猫
5 TV slash iai be welcome to the show
5テレビスラッシュ はショーに 歓迎 される
hey everybody I'm Robby
こんにちは、私はRobbyです
I'm Sasha and I'm Jeff how have you guys
私はSashaです、そして私は Jeffです
been so good are you ready for this yes
とても良い、あなたがこのイエスのために準備ができている となって
it's Wednesday our time now you might be
今は 水曜日 です。
watching this on Saturday Sunday Tuesday
土曜日にこれを見ています日曜日火曜日
some a year from now there may be
今から1年後があるかもしれません
they've added an eighth day to the
彼らは 8 日目を 追加しまし た
calendar because you're watching this
これを 見て いるのでカレンダー
157 thousand years in the future right
将来の 157千年の 権利
whoo cat 5 day that would be music but
Whoo cat 5日は 音楽だけど
for us this is this is the middle of the
私たちにとってこれはこれが真ん中です
week for us in the studio live and I
私たちのスタジオでの一週間のライブと私
look forward to this moment every week
毎週この瞬間を楽しみにして
as do I this week's gonna be fun too
私 も今週 も楽しいことになる でしょう
it should be a lot of great stuff to
それは多くの素晴らしいものになるはずです
look at it should be fun yeah I don't
それを 見るの は楽しいはずです
think we've ever not had fun agreed so
私たちはこれまでに 同意し た楽しみがなかったと思います
read it would be really sad after 559
559 以降は本当に悲しい でしょう
episodes to blow that streak 559
そのストリーク559を爆破するエピソード
episodes whoa Jeff I know Robbie and I
Jeff 私はRobbieと 私が 知っているエピソード
did have like a five episode streak
5エピソードストリークが好きでしたか
where every time we tried to do
毎回しようと したところ
something I pretty much brackets I think
何か私が思う私はかなりカッコ
that was like the technical difficulty
それは技術的な 難しさのようでした
month where you know blame it on the
あなたが上でそれを非難 知っ月
positioning of the moon or something
月か何か のポジショニング
like something yeah but we're not having
何か のように 、ええ、私たちは持っていません
any of that we broke that streak and now
いずれにしても 我々はそのストリークを破った
we're on to awesome shows oh yeah now
我々は今 、 そうそう素晴らしいショーに にしています
we're in the streak of awesome nice so
私たちはすごいすてきなのストリークにいる
you are here just in the nick of time
あなたはちょうど 時間 の ニックネームでここにいます
for the streak of awesome shows let's
すごい番組のために
get some housekeeping out of the way
邪魔にならないようにいくつかのハウスキーピングを入手
yeah first of all category 5 TV apparel
ええ最初のすべてのカテゴリ5のTVアパレル
is available at camp 5 dot TV slash
キャンプ 5ドットテレビスラッシュで利用可能です。
shirts and thank you to everybody who
シャツと みんなに ありがとう
has picked up a category-5 t-shirt or a
カテゴリー5の Tシャツか、
new everyday t-shirt even we've got the
私たちも持っている新しい日常のTシャツ
new kid on the block change we joked
私たちが冗談を言ったブロック変更の新しい子供
about and it's actually a thing and get
について、それは実際にものです
it a cap five TV slash shirts it's a
それ はキャップ 5 テレビスラッシュシャツです
really cool way to support the category
カテゴリをサポートする本当にクールな方法
five dot TV network what we do here is
我々はここで何をすべきか 5つのドットのテレビネットワークで あります
we create family-friendly broadcasts
私たちは家族向けの放送を作成します
that are available to you your family
あなたはあなたの家族に利用可能です
your friends everywhere in the world
世界中の あなたの友達
absolutely free that's what we do in
絶対に無料 です。
order to do that we have to be able to
私たちのことができるよう に する必要があることを行うため
fund the thing and it costs a lot of
物事に資金を供給し、それはたくさんの費用がかかります
money so you're able to support that by
お金は でこれをサポートする ことができますので、
buying t-shirts by buying products that
その製品を購入してTシャツを購入する
we show on the show by using our links
私達は私達のリンク を使っ て ショーに出演する
and by using our partner links off of
そして私達のパートナーリンクを使用して
our website things like that and of
私達のウェブサイトの事そのようなもの
course you can become a patron and there
もちろん、あなたがパトロンとなり 、そこに することができます
are a variety of ways that you can
あなたができるさまざまな方法があります
support us more information is on our
私達を支えなさいより多くの 情報は私達にある
website category five dot TV nice we
ウェブサイトのカテゴリ5ドットテレビいい ね
also do have some editions of ded effect
デッド 効果のいくつかのエディションもありますか
to VR left to give away
VRへ
not very many a limited number of data
限られた数のデータではない
factors like this and it's like Downton
このような要因とそれはDowntonのようなものです
like that means many of you are winners
そのようにあなたの多くが 勝者 であることを意味します
already if you find yourself not in that
あなたは その 中で自分自身を 見つけ ていない 場合は 、既に
position you are not yet a winner here
あなた はまだ ここで は勝者 で はありません
is how you become one you email category
あなたがどのようにあなたがあなたのカテゴリーにEメールするのか
five TV or to the interwebs will find
5つのテレビまたは 網間に見つけるでしょう
its way to us contest at category five
私たちへの道はカテゴリー5で 競う
TV that sounds more realist ats but
よりリアルな雰囲気のテレビ
that's a real address oh yes know who
それは、 ああ知っている実際のアドレスです
you are where you're watching from what
あなたは何から 見ている場所です
you're watching on questions comments
質問コメントを見ている
thoughts concerns and will enter you
懸念 を 考え 、あなたに入ります
into the draw to win one of our very few
私達の非常に少数の1つに勝つために引き分けに
remaining copies that affect who we are
私たち が 誰である かに 影響を与える残りのコピー
wonderful
素晴らしい
mmm-hmm and if you don't feel like
そしてあなたの よう に感じていない場合は MMM-HMM
hanging on the VR world you can check us
あなたは 私たち をチェックすることができます VRの世界にぶら下がって
out on google play music that's right we
グーグルで音楽 を 演奏 する
are on there so you want to go to
あなたがに行きたいので、そこ にあります
category five TV slash subscribe now
カテゴリ5 TVスラッシュ今すぐ登録
lots of good stuff there yeah you can
たくさんの良いものがあります
subscribe to any of our shows as a
として私たちのショーのいずれかを 購読 する
matter of fact so yeah we're category
実際のところそうそう私達は部門です
five technology TV Jeff and Lawrence is
5つのテクノロジーテレビジェフ とローレンス は
new every day we've got a couple of
新しい私たちは の カップルを持っている毎日
other shows there incidentally we're
偶然にもそこに他のショー
going to be looking at a product tonight
今夜商品を見に 行く
to help you to sleep and nature sounds
あなたが眠るの を 助け、自然の音
are a great way to do that we have a
私たちが持っていることを行うための素晴らしい方法です
name
名
sure sounds program that's right
確かに正しいプログラムを鳴らす
immersive nature sounds you can actually
没入型の自然はあなたが実際にできるように聞こえます
tune in to not just the video but the
ビデオだけでなく、
audio and it's immersive so it's
それは没入型のオーディオです
recorded in binaural 3d audio if you
バイノーラル3Dオーディオで録音した場合
wear headphones or what we're gonna show
ヘッドフォンを着用するか、 表示する 予定のもの
you tonight you can hear everything
あなたは今夜あなたは すべて を聞くことができ ます
around you so really what it's about is
あなたの周りにいるので、実際には
we're hooking you up to completely
私たちはあなたを完全にフックしています
disconnect from the real world
現実世界から切断する
audio-visual at the VR who needs people
人を必要とするVRでの視聴覚
I mean people Jeff I am people yeah
私は人ですジェフ私は人ですね
these are our friends that we're hanging
これらは私たちがぶら下がっている私たちの友達です
out with right now I know through
今で外に私が通過知っています
digital means yes yes no terms that's
デジタルという意味はいはいいいえ
right
右
did you know your morgue okay so last
あなたの 遺体安置所を知っていますか
week we cover the PT or a couple weeks
私達はPT か2週間 をカバーする 週
ago people we camera yes yes so we have
前の人々私たちはカメラはいはいそう私たちは持っています
an update on it about an adapter yeah do
アダプタ についての最新情報
you remember we I showed what I soldered
ハンダ付けしたものを見せたのを覚えている
myself so we got this p OE adapter that
私自身はこのp OE アダプターを
means power over ethernet so we've got
我々は持っているので、イーサネット上の電力を意味する
this great PTZ camera all these short
この素晴らしいPTZカメラはすべてこれらの短いです
forms right great tech show all these
これらすべてを形作る優れたハイテクフォーム
short forms PTZ is pan tilt zoom so you
ショートフォーム PTZはパンチルトズームなので
think about a camera that can pan left
左にパンできるカメラを考える
and right tilt up and down and zoom so
上下に傾けてズームする
in and out so PTZ camera that's what it
内外にPTZカメラがある
represents it means you can digitally
それはあなたがデジタル的にできることを意味します
through an app or through a program on
アプリまたは プログラム を通じて
your computer a web browser you can
あなたのコンピュータ は あなた ができる ウェブ ブラウザです
control the positioning in the zoom of
ズームの位置を制御
our camera it's great but one of the
私たちのカメラは、それは素晴らしいことだが、 の 1
things with it is that you've got to
それとの事はあなたが持っているということです
have not only Ethernet or Wi-Fi network
イーサネットやWi-Fiネットワークだけではありません
connectivity but you also have to have
接続性しかしあなたはまた持っている必要があります
power to it right and so that means this
それに力を正しくそしてそう それはこれを意味する
wall wart that's got to be plugged in
差し込まれることになっている壁いぼ
and then plugged into the camera well I
それから 私は よくカメラに差し込ん だ
came up with this with this little
これで少し 思いつい た
dongle that would convert power over
パワーを変換する ドングル
ethernet from a from a surveillance
監視からのイーサネット
camera of all things okay to work with
すべてのものをカメラで操作しても大丈夫
the PTZ camera we were reviewing which
私達が検討していたPTZカメラ
you can find out more about and actually
もっと詳しく知ることができます
get the the device cat5 dot TV slash PTZ
デバイスを入手する cat5 dot TVスラッシュ PTZ
but then one of my friends brett he
しかし、それから 私の友人の 一人 が彼を虐待します
found a device on Amazon which we've now
Amazonで私たちが今持っているデバイスを 見つけまし た
added to that link so you can pick it up
あなた が それ を拾う こと が できる ようにそのリンクに追加されました
directly because not everybody has the
誰もが持っているわけではないから直接
mad soldering skills of Robbie you know
あなたが知っているロビーの狂ったはんだ付け技術
and I'm Sam
そして私はサムです
you've seen my soldering skills loose
あなたは私のはんだ付け技術がゆるいのを見ました
definition you have okay I mean mad like
定義あなたは大丈夫だ 私は怒っているという意味
you know Mad Hatter okay no I saw in a
あなたはMad Hatterを知っています
matter of seven days you like it proved
あなたがそれを証明したような 7日間の問題
by like a hundred percent she's the
百パーセントのように、 彼女は
kindest person in the world you started
あなたが始めた世界で最も親切な人
from the bottom now you're here started
下から今、あなたはここから始めました
from the bottom now here so Brett found
今ここから下から、ブレットは見つけました
an adapter on Amazon that is exactly
Amazonのアダプタは正確に
what I created but it's like two bucks
私が作成したものですが、それは2ドルのようなものです
the one I made cost 6 bucks and the one
私が作ったものは6ドル、もう1つはコストがかかりました。
I made is this like 3-inch dong 4 inch
私は作った3インチドン4インチのようなこれです
dongle this one is just like a little
これはちょっと 似ている
tip that you just plug on to the adapter
アダプタに差し込むだけのヒント
wah
ワウ
so here you go it exists but if you if
だからここにあなたはそれが存在します行く が あなたが
you do like size to price ratio it's a
あなたはそれがだ 価格比の大き好きです
better value for you know how many
あなたにとってより良い価値
dollars per end of the adapter so this
アダプタの端あたりのドルはそうこれ
thing is is going to allow you to use
事はあなたが 使用 できるようにするつもりです
power over ethernet on the PTZ camera
PTZカメラのイーサネット経由の電源
that we reviewed right and it's like
私たちが正しくレビューしたようなものです。
it's all pre fin dangled so you don't
それはすべてぶら下がっているので、あなたは違います。
have to be a master soldering guru so
そうマスターはんだ付けの達人でなければなりません
sarcastic watch that episode check it
そのエピソードが それをチェックする皮肉な時計
out how many episodes have I messed up
いくつのエピソードをめちゃくちゃにしたか
soldering on ya know if you do have that
あなたがそれを持って いる かどうかを知って屋にはんだ付け
PTZ camera maybe you're monitoring it
PTZカメラはおそらくそれを監視している
through your enterprise server and you
あなたのエンタープライズサーバとあなたを通して
need some software to help you with that
それを助けるためにいくつかのソフトウェア が必要です
I've heard that there's a great version
私は素晴らしいバージョンがあると聞いた
of Nemzek do you know anything about
Nemzek について
that like to tell if the camera is up
カメラが 起動 しているかどうかを確認するのが好きです
and running well just anything to
そして 何でも するために よく走る
monitor your server do I know anything I
あなたのサーバーを監視し、私は私が何を知っていますか
know any conversion 1.4 perhaps how well
1.4の 変換を知っている
names 1.4 is gaming it's like on the
名前1.4は、 それが上の ような ゲームです
threshold of release I've been loving
私が愛してきたリリースの限界
the updates oh if you don't follow me on
あああなた が私に従っていない 場合はああ更新
Twitter you've got who at Robbie
あなたがロビーで誰を持っているのTwitter
Ferguson and names 1.4 so this is a
ファーガソンと1.4という名前なのでこれは
enterprise monitoring server for the
エンタープライズ監視サーバ
Raspberry Pi so with a Raspberry Pi
ラズベリーパイとラズベリーパイ
microcomputer you can monitor all your
あなたはあなたのすべてを監視することができますマイクロコンピュータ
devices and find out what's up what's
デバイスと何が起きているのかを調べる
down with having problems yeah if hard
難しい場合は問題を抱えて
drive space is low it'll warn me of that
ドライブのスペースが足り ない という 警告 が表示される
kind of stuff it's fantastic but it's
一種のものそれは 素晴らしいですが、それは
really evolved over the years there's
本当に あります 長年 にわたって 進化
been so much community support it's been
多くのコミュニティの支援を受けています
a lot of fun to do but now is 1.4 I'm so
やることはたくさんありますが、今は1.4です
excited about a Jeff
ジェフに興奮
okay I'm Ashley you need this at your
大丈夫、私はAshleyです
office yes I do think about this
オフィスはい私はこれについて考えていますか
it's a Raspberry Pi yes that will tell
それが教えてくれるラズベリーパイはぎました
you if your chiropractic software hasn't
あなたのカイロプラクティックソフトウェアがそうでないならあなたは
run its every scan Tara scan since May
スキャン ごと タラ月以来、スキャン の実行
30th okay yeah could you imagine it'll
30 大丈夫そうだね想像できるだろう
warn you before it happens it's
それはだ が起こる 前に警告を表示
happening so you get emails and you know
起こっているので、あなたは電子メールを取得し、 あなたが 知っている
that this is happening that something is
これが起こっ て いる ということ
going wrong before it actually goes
実際に行く前にうまくいかない
wrong it becomes critical I do need that
間違っていることが重要 になります
two drives in a raid one one of them has
それらの1つが持っているRAIDの2つのドライブ
failed and you may not know and maybe
失敗し、あなたは知らないかもしれないし、多分
you're not monitoring it on a regular
あなたは定期的にそれを監視していません
basis so it will alert you that one of
それはあなた の1つに 警告します ので、基礎
those drives has failed those kinds of
それらのドライブはこれらの種類の失敗しました
things see I I look at my network at
IIで私のネットワークを見ているもの
home and I go I haven't had a need for
家に帰ると私は行く必要がなかった
NEMS because all of our devices are used
当社の すべての 機器が使用されている ためNEMS
and then I got into crypto currency and
それから私は 暗号通貨に入りました 、そして
I've been mining turquoi with my know
私は知っていると私はターコイを採掘してきた
that your minor is that that's correct
あなたの未成年者はそれが正しいということです
it's completely headless and so every
それは 完全にヘッドレスだからすべての
once while login I'm like oh how am i
一度ログインしている間私はああ好きです
aspirated zero what
ゼロ に何を 吸引
oh no I've been down and I have no clue
ああ、 私は ダウンし て いると 私は手がかりがない
for how long right so I'm being able to
どれぐらいの 長さなので
monitor your hash rates on the miner yep
鉱夫 うん 上のハッシュ率を 監視
and be able to keep track yeah I mean
そして私は トラック を続けることができ ます
what we did who did you and I we already
私たちがした こと 誰が あなた をしたか私は 私たちはすでに
are I know what happened wait you know
私は あなたが知っている待って何が起こったのかを知っています
we fell out last week that's why he
私たちは、 なぜ彼だと先週落ちました
wasn't here it's true yeah we're working
ここにはありませんでした
like the middle child I was born to be
私が生まれて生まれた中年の子供のように
what why are you guys middle our best
何故あなた達は私達の最善の真ん中なのですか
friends and where am I because numbs you
私の友達はどこ ですか
you are the Nexus together okay
あなたは一緒に大丈夫ネクサスです
sustained
持続した
check out names linux.com but why I'm so
linux.comの 名前を調べてみてください
excited about this is because with
この興奮は して いるため であります
version 1.4 Sacha best friend Sasha yes
バージョン1.4 Sacha の親友Sashaはい
yeah the the product has evolved so much
うん、 製品はそんなに進化してきた
and I call it a product because it
私は それので 、製品それを呼び出します
really is a commercial application but
本当に商用アプリケーションですが
it's free is free
無料です
change that's how we two things and
それが私たち2つのこと
that's why we have so much trouble
だからこそ私たちは多くの問題を抱えています
paying the bills we do awesome things
私たちは素晴らしいことをする手形を支払う
and give it away but MEMS 1.4 is coming
それを諦めても MEMS 1.4が やってくる
and it's like we've got the attention of
そして私たちが注目を集めているようなものです。
Nagios we've got them writing about it
Nagios私たちが彼らにそれ について書い てもらった
we've got people talking about it that
それについて話して いる人がいる
are in the industry and at min magazine
業界 では と分の雑誌で あります
has actually published a full like eight
実際に8のようなフルを公開しています
page color article about it well talk
それについてのページの色の記事は よく話します
and like this is all happening as I'm
私のようにこれがすべて起こっているように
just kind of like doing this in my spare
私の予備でこれをするのと同じようなもの
time when you know tinker time not now
ティンカーの時間を今知っている時間
category 5 &amp; M's that's and family time
カテゴリ5＆Mのことと家族の時間
like this is my spare time so with 1.4 I
これは私の暇な時間であるように1.4 I とそう
did something crazy Jeff okay nems was
何か変なことをしたJeff
always based on naggy oh and Nagios pie
いつもナギオス と Nagiosパイに基づいて
right okay so this is a raspberry pie
これで ラズベリーパイです
distro of Nagios so it was based on that
Nagiosのディストリビューションなのでそれに基づいて いた
and then I built it up over the years
それから私は長年かけてそれを構築しました
and it's been getting better and better
そしてそれは どんどん 良くなっています
right name's 1.4 I blasted everything
正しい 名前の1.4すべてを非難した
that's ever been done wiped it
それは一掃されました
completely started from scratch and
完全にゼロから開始し、
built it compiled it from the ground up
ゼロから作り上げた
so if you're familiar with Nagios this
なので、Nagiosに慣れているならこれ
is like version 4.3 point for this is
これはバージョン4.3のポイントのようなものです
the the best web based responsive
最高の Web ベースのレスポンシブ
interface for nagios that you've ever
あなたは今まできたのnagiosのためのインターフェース
seen and the capability of doing all
見られ、 すべて をする能力
your administration through a GUI and
GUIによる管理
you don't have to deal with Nagios
Nagios に対処する必要はありません
scripting right it's a beautiful it's
それは美しいです
amazing so that's what Nemus 1.4
すごいので、 Nemus 1.4
represents we've got backers like logic
ロジックのような 支援者を得たことを表します
supply this is a computer manufacturer
これはコンピュータの製造元です
that is providing hardware so that we
我々はその ように は 、ハードウェアを提供しています
can bring nems to their hardware so that
ように彼らのハードウェアにNEMSをもたらすことができます
we can bring it to you as an appliance
私達は電気器具としてあなたにそれを持って来ることができます
we've got people like the manufacturers
メーカーのような人がいます
of fit lit to check them out the it's
それをチェックアウトするための フィット感
all one word fit let - it's a fully
すべて一つの単語フィット LET -それは完全です
integrated no moving parts completely
可動部品を完全に統合していない
solid-state computer and this little
ソリッドステートコンピュータとこの小さな
itty bitty thing it's like a million
ちょっとしたことそれは百万のようなものです
times better than a Raspberry Pi as far
ラズベリーパイよりもはるかに良い
as its actual power goes and it's being
その実際の力が行くにつれて、それは
MEMS is being ported to that this thing
MEMSはこのことに移植されています
that I built and gave away for free
私は 自由のために 構築され、 離れて与えました
they're putting it on that and
彼らはその上で、それを入れている と、
selling these devices that's cool that
これらの機器を売っているのはかっこいい
is so cool there's so much exciting
そんなにエキサイティングあります ので、 クール です
things coming from Nagios enterprise
Nagios 企業 から来るもの
monitoring server and I'm excited that
監視サーバーと私は興奮している
we're gonna be showing it on the show
私たちはショー で それを 見せ ているつもりです
pretty soon as well this is coming it's
もうすぐ これ がやってくる
coming updates have made me very like
今後のアップデートで私は 非常に好きになった
anticipatory it's been neat seeing it
それを見 て きちんとして いる
evolve because Nagios has traditionally
Nagiosが伝統的に持っていたので進化する
been very onerous - yeah maintain and to
非常に煩わしかった - ええ保守して
get up and going and it can be a
立ち上がって行くとそれはすることができます
nightmare for a sysadmin to create an
を作成するためのシステム管理者の ための悪夢
audio server and get it up and going
オーディオサーバーと立ち上げ
create the scripts get monitoring five
スクリプトを作成する
minutes you're done they can live white
あなたがやった分彼らは 白く 生きることができます
for everyone and it's all based on a GUI
みんなのために、それはすべてGUIに基づいています
and a web user interface with responsive
とレスポンシブ Webユーザー インターフェイス
layouts that works on your mobile phone
お使いの携帯電話 上で 動作レイアウト
or your tablet yep what you definitely
または あなたの タブレットうん あなたは間違いなく何を
need to check it out folks and e/m n an
それを人々 に チェックしてもらう必要があります。
EMS Linux com
EMS Linux com
ok ready to get into the show yes that
はい ショー に それを 取得する準備ができて、[OK]
was like just housekeeping but I get
ただのハウスキーピングみたいだった けど
excited about really cool projects that
本当にクールなプロジェクトに興奮して
we've got going on I mean Plex pies
私たちは起こっています私はプレックス パイ を意味する
another one where we started talking on
私達が話し始めたもう一つ
the show of them putting Plex on a
プレックスを身に着けている彼らのショー
Raspberry Pi and so then I imaged it and
ラズベリーパイと 私は それ をイメージした
gave it out yeah now there's like
それを出したええ 今今のようにあります
hundreds of people that are using my
私を使っている何百人もの人々
image of Plex
プレックスの画像
on a Raspberry Pi that's how it's
ラズベリーパイでは
evolved yeah that's how we use it at
進化したええそれは我々がそれを使用する方法です
home and actually I've got some friends
家と実際に私は 何人かの友達 が います
who live in Malawi Africa they go they
マラウイアフリカ に 住んでいる 人
have our guest access so they're
ゲストアクセスがあるので
constantly checking out the stuff on my
常に 私 のものをチェックアウトする
network Wow
ネットワークうわー
through a Raspberry Pi it's beautiful
ラズベリーパイを通してそれは美しい
nice so flex pay is another example so
素敵なので、フレックス給料はとても別の例であります
that's kind of what's neat about this
それはこのことについてすごいことのようなものです
show so we'll show you something this is
これ で 何かを 見せて あげる
so you know some of the things we're
だから、あなたは私たちがいることのいくつかを知っている
showing you tonight you got to buy if
今夜あなたが買うようになったことを示す
you want to get your hands on it but a
手に入れたいのです が
lot of the things we're gonna show you
私たちが あなたに 見せようとしていることの多く
how to do things and then we're gonna
物事をどうやってやるか、そして我々はつもりだ
take what we did and package it up and
私たちがしたことを取り、それをパッケージ化して
give it to you as a download and it's
ダウンロードとしてあなたに それを与える 、それはです
free and you know you can get it and how
無料で 入手でき ます。
cool is that very I can't think of too
私はあまりにも考えることができないということはクールです
many TV shows that that do that kind of
そのようなことをする 多くのテレビ番組
stuff
もの
maybe there's lots coming up one yeah
多分1つ来るそうたくさんあります
just ours oh that's just our eating job
ちょうど 私たちのものああ それだけで私たちの 食事の 仕事
hmm all right so we've got a couple of
うーん 、すべての 権利私たちは夫婦の持っています
things we're looking at today what are
私たちが 何で ある かを、今日見 ているもの
we looking at first well we're gonna get
我々は最初に よく見て我々は得るつもりだ
to the product that we're looking at
私たちが見ている製品へ
right because these things have been
これらのことが され て いる ので 正しい
sent to us to review we've got to do it
確認するために送信さ れました
it's like an obligation but they're cool
義務のようですが、かっこいいです
things that we want to show you but
私たち があなたに見せ たいもの
before we get into it
私達がそれに入る前に
Sasha yes have you ever been on Facebook
Sasha はい 、あなた は Facebookに参加した ことがありますか
in the past I have been on Facebook or
過去に私はFacebookにいたか
email often on email and has anyone like
メールに頻繁に電子メールなどで 誰を 持っています
your husband or someone said what's the
あなたの夫や誰かが何を言っている
password to this or what's the what's
これへのパスワードまたはなに がなにか
your credit card number any of this kind
この種類のあなたのクレジットカード番号
of information that you would never send
あなたが送信しないだろう と の情報 の
over face just add this today on the way
向こうにはちょうど途中で これを 今日 追加する
here my wife called me and what is she
ここで私の妻は私を呼んだそして彼女は何ですか
saying she's like I need to know that
私 はそれ を 知っ ている 必要 がある ように彼女は言う
password and what did have you ever had
パスワードとあなたが今まで持っていたもの
that happen I think so maybe we can't
それが起こるのではないかと思います
pinpoint an exact moment in time Jeff
時間 ジェフ での正確な瞬間を特定
can tell because it's tomorrow asking me
明日は私に聞いているので言うことができます
but like I can't think of a time that's
しかし、私はそれが 時間 を 考えることができないように
right
右
but today so she said what's the
しかし今日、彼女は何を言った
password to that thing yeah and the best
そのことへのパスワードええと最高の
part is I'm going try this try this try
この部分を試してみるこれを試してみる
this try this you're giving her all this
この本を 試してみてください 、あなたは彼女のすべてを与えています
we had 16 different options and none of
私たちは16の異なるオプションを持っていたがどれも
them worked none of them worked okay but
彼らはうまくいきませんでした
now you've given out as many of your
今、あなたはあなたの 多くのもの を配った
passwords as you can think of yes so who
あなたはそうはいを考えることができるようなパスワード
knows what those passwords are for and
これらのパスワードが何のためにあるのか知っている
there's this thing called a
これと呼ばれるものがあります
man-in-the-middle attack and what that
中間者攻撃とそのこと
means is okay so I'm the man in the
手段は大丈夫ですので、私は 中に 男です
middle Sasha yes could you tell Jeff
中サーシャそうジェフに言ってもらえますか
your password oh my password is password
あなたのパスワードああ私の パスワードはpasswordです
yeah password one two three can you hear
ええパスワード1 2 3 あなたは聞くことができます
that password 1 2 3 yeah I heard that
そのパスワード 1 2 3ええ 、私は それを 聞きました
too because I'm the man in the middle
私も 真ん中の男 だから
right and so if I go into a public Wi-Fi
私が 公衆Wi-Fi にアクセスするならば
hotspot right so I'm sitting at a coffee
ホットスポットなので コーヒーを飲みながら 座って いる
shop I've got my phone and I'm doing
私は自分の電話を持って いて、やっています
what I think is a private conversation
プライベート 会話 だと思います
well I'm actually who's the man in the
私は実際には誰 が
middle well the coffee shop or anyone
真ん中のコーヒーショップ か誰か
who's on that same Wi-Fi network because
誰がその同じWi-Fiネットワークにいるのか
now remember as soon as you connect to
今すぐに接続するとすぐに覚えて
the same network Jeff you're on the same
同じネットワークJeffあなたが同じ上にいる
local area network as I am right so you
私は あなたの ための右だと、ローカル・エリア・ネットワーク
have a local IP address and you're able
ローカルIP アドレスを持っていれば可能です
to monitor traffic that is happening
発生しているトラフィックを監視する
from my device
私の端末から
correct ok so man in the middle says I
大丈夫そうで真ん中の男は私に言う
can hear what you're saying
あなたが言っていることを聞くことができます
so you just shared your 16 passwords and
16個のパスワードを共有した
I can hear it because I'm the man in the
私は私の中の男だから私はそれを聞くことができます
middle
中間
well what if there was a service that's
そのサービスがあったらどうでしょう
absolutely free that kind of helps with
そのようなものの助けとなるのは絶対に無料
that by saying okay only one person can
一人だけ が 大丈夫 と言うことによって
hear this and when Jeff here's your
これを聞いて、Jeffがここにいるとき
password I'm gonna destroy all records
パスワードすべてのレコードを破棄します
of what you said right okay
あなたが言ったことについて
that would be wonderful do you remember
それは素晴らしいだろうあなたは覚えていますか
Maxwell Smart yes the shoe phone yeah
マクスウェルスマートはい靴電話はい
and what was it like the exploding hears
そして それが爆発 聞こえ どの ような ものでした
everything
すべてのもの
yeah here's here's the path here's the
ええ、これはここにありますパスはここにあります
secret message or even you know what was
秘密のメッセージ、あるいはあなたも 知って いた
it tuned to there's a cartoon get you
それは漫画があなたを取得することがあるように調整しました
next time gadget Inspector Gadget yes
次回ガジェットインスペクタ ガジェット はい
I'll get you next time gadget he was the
私は彼がだった次回のガジェットを取得します
same in so this message will
同じようにこのメッセージは
self-destruct and chief Quimby and
自己破壊的な チーフ
employees got burned exactly right so
従業員はまさにその通りにやけどした
there's a service that you can bring up
あなたが育てることができる サービス があります
just strictly through your web browser
Webブラウザを介して厳密に
and how cool would it be if you could
あなたができれ ば、それはどのようにクールになり
have a one time message that you said
あなたが言ったワンタイムメッセージを持っている
and if it if it was called a one time
そしてそれが一度だけ呼ばれたら
message wouldn't it be right that it
メッセージはそれが正しいというわけではないでしょう
would be one time in your browser so the
ので、お使いのブラウザで1時間になります
number one T Y dot M e so you head on
ナンバーワンのTYドットM e
over there and I say okay well my
あそこに 私は 大丈夫 と言っ て
password Jeff is password 1 2 3 and then
password Jeffはpassword 1 2 3です。
I generate the link and now it's going
私はリンクを生成し、そして今それは行きます
to allow me to send that link so I can
できる ように リンク を 送信 できる ように する
copy that link and I can now email that
そのリンクをコピーすれば私 は今それを電子メールで送る こと ができます
to my friend Jeff or send it to him by
私の友人ジェフにまたはそれによって彼にそれを送る
text send it to him by Facebook or
テキストはFacebookで彼 にそれ を 送る か
however I want to do it now Jeff
しかし私は今それをやりたいジェフ
receives that link and he clicks on it
そのリンクを受け取り、彼はそれをクリックします
and it says this message will
そしてそれはこのメッセージが
self-destruct now notice I'm connected
自己破壊しているの がわかります
over a secure connection so everything
安全な接続を介して
that I typed their password 1 2 3 was
パスワード を入力 したこと1 2 3
encrypted going to the server and
暗号化されたサーバーに行く と、
because of the nature of their service
彼らの奉仕の性質上
we make that very valid assumption that
その非常に有効な仮定を立てます。
they're encrypting it on their end as
彼らは自分の側でそれを暗号化しています
well right but the communication that's
うまく右しかしだ通信
happening here is completely encrypted
ここ で 起こる こと は完全に暗号化されています
so if we jump back to Jeff's note that
そのため、Jeffの話に戻ります。
he is open now we can view that note and
彼は今開いてい ますそのメモ を 見ることができます
there's the note that I just sent Jeff
私がちょうどジェフを送ったというメモがあります
my password is password 1 2 3 but
私のパスワードはパスワード1 2 3ですが
wait some man in the middle has access
途中で誰かがアクセスできるのを待つ
to that URL that I just sent Jeff and so
私がちょうどJeffに送ったそのURLへ
they click on it and it says hey hold up
彼らはそれをクリックして、それはちょっと我慢して言う
the note you're trying to view was
表示しようとしているメモは
already accessed notes may only be
すでにアクセスされたメモは
viewed once and then they all destroyed
一度見て、それからそれらはすべて破壊されました
one T Y dot m e one time just like that
1 T Yは、ちょうど その ように私に1時間に点在しました
one time one time I had the whole time
私は全体の時間を持っていた 1時間 1時間
not even less I'm just song great
それほど 小さくない私はただの 歌
service
サービス
check it out Jeff what have we got
それをチェックしてください
coming up after the break ok so coming
大丈夫そう休憩の後に上がる
up after the break we are going to take
休憩の後に起きます
a look at an Android TV stick it has
それが持っているAndroidのTVスティックを 見て
significantly significantly better Wi-Fi
かなり大幅に優れたWi-Fi
than the newest Raspberry Pi Oh better
最新のラズベリーパイ ああ よりも 良いです
frame rates on the video platforms like
ビデオプラットフォームのフレームレート
YouTube and just straight-up cool nice
YouTubeとただのストレートクール
awesome stick around
素晴らしいスティック
[Music]
[音楽]
for a limited time get your hands on
限られた時間のためにあなたの手を取ります
limited-edition shirts from the category
このカテゴリの限定版シャツ
5 TV network these high quality shirts
5つのTVネットワークこれらの 高品質のシャツ
are manufactured by teespring a
a をteespring すること によって製造されています
fundraising website and your purchase
募金ウェブサイトとあなたの購入
will help support the shows we produce
私達が作り出すショーを支えるのを助けます
get yours today and send us your
今日あなたのものを入手して私たちにあなたのものを送りなさい
pictures to be featured on the
で紹介 さ れる写真
corresponding show visit cap 5 dot TV
対応するショー訪問キャップ5ドットテレビ
slash shirts to support us and get your
私達を支え 、あなたの もの を手に入れるためにシャツを切る
official Network shirt today cap five
公式ネットワークシャツ今日キャップ 5
dot TV slash shirts welcome back this is
ドットテレビスラッシュシャツ歓迎これはです
category five technology TV y'all ready
カテゴリー5テクノロジーTV
yep we're gonna get into an Android TV
うん私たちは Androidのテレビに 入るつもりです
stick now I've got my Amazon fire TV
今スティック私は私のアマゾンの火災テレビを持っています
stick okay and to be honest we haven't
大丈夫だと正直に言うと私たちはしていない
been Buber impressed with it right first
ブーバーは、 右の最初の それと感銘を受け て
of all something that is incredibly
信じられないほどすべてのもののうち
lacking from the Amazon fire TV stick
アマゾン火災テレビスティックから欠けている
there it is
そこにそれがある
do you notice it okay there's a power
あなたはそれが大丈夫だということに気づきますか
Inlet but where is the USB where's the
インレットだがどこにUSBがある
capability to to plug in a keyboard or a
キーボードやキーボードを接続する機能
mouse or a receiver of any sort yeah how
マウスまたは任意の並べ替えの受信方法ええ
do you you don't Jeff you don't
あなたはしませんかジェフはしません
oh okay it has it has bluetooth so you
ああ大丈夫それは あなたがそうブルートゥースを 持って います
can do things with compatible Bluetooth
互換性のあるBluetoothでできること
devices but all in all I mean it's an OK
デバイスだが全部で私はそれが大丈夫だという意味
device but for the price I think it
デバイスが価格のために私 はそれ を 考える
would be nicer to have a more robust
より堅牢にするほうがよいでしょう
Android powered solution and this is
Android搭載ソリューションでこれは
Android power the Amazon fire TV stick
Androidの電源は、Amazonの火災テレビスティック
but it's like branded Amazon is
しかし、それはAmazonのブランドのようなものです。
proprietary in a lot of ways and the
多くの 点で独自の
fact that the hardware is so locked down
ハードウェアがとてもロックされているという事実
is pretty poor to me now the other thing
私にとってはかなり貧弱です
about the fire TV stick like the
火の ような テレビ スティックについて
Raspberry Pi of all generations that
そのすべての世代のラズベリーパイ
include Wi-Fi doesn't have very good
Wi-Fiを含むのはあまり良くない
Wi-Fi okay and my Wi-Fi in the house is
Wi-Fiは大丈夫で、家の中の私のWi-Fiは
not the greatest but it's pretty good
ない 最大の それはかなり 良いこと です
and I would
そして私は
that it should work on the TV that's you
それはあなたのテレビで動作するはずです
know only about 30 feet away one floor
1階から約30フィートだけ知っている
above right but it doesn't work that
右の上のそれは それは 動作しません。
great
すばらしいです
that's unfortunate so it's a little
それは残念なので少しです
disappointing in the Raspberry Pi same
ラズベリーパイ と同じ 残念
thing so we set out to find a device
なので、私たち はデバイス を 見つける ために着手し まし た
that had better Wi-Fi and just Android
それはより良いWi-FiとただのAndroidを持っていた
something that we can bring up YouTube
YouTubeを立ち上げることができるもの
and the kids can watch their shows and
そして子供たちは彼らのショーを見ることができます
stuff because to connect a Windows
Windowsに接続するためのもの
computer like a set-top windows system
セットトップウィンドウシステムのようなコンピュータ
or something like that now I've got to
またはそのようなもの 今私はしなければならない
get antivirus for it which I'm not
私はしていないそれのためにアンチウイルスを入手
opposed to but I have to worry about the
反対したが、私は 心配する 必要 は あり
kids accidentally clicking on something
子供が誤って何かをクリックした
that is now malware because you know my
あなたは私のことを知っているのでそれは今マルウェアです
my seven year old he just searches I
私の7 歳の彼はただ私を検索します
wanted him to look up a video on YouTube
YouTubeで ビデオを見てもらいたかった
the other day and I told him what to
先日、私 は彼に何をすべきかを言った
search for and he started searching for
検索し、彼は探し始めた
it in the address bar rather than on
ではなく、アドレスバーにそれを
youtube.com so he's seven years old I'm
youtube.comだから彼は7歳です
trying to teach him that hey that's not
そうではないことを彼に教えることを試みる
the way you do it son but when he does
あなたはそれの息子が、彼はないやり方
and he clicks on the wrong link of the
そして彼はの間違ったリンクをクリックします
10,000 results in Google it's going to
Google で 1万件の結果
take you to something less your computer
あなたのコンピュータ より少ないものに連れて行って
is infected with a virus you've probably
おそらくウイルスに感染している
seen you know all these things and then
あなたはすべてのこれらの事を知っていると見
oh well ok so click click click and all
まあまあいいので、クリッククリッククリック すべて
of a sudden now you're really infected
突然、あなたは 本当に感染し ています
with a virus because you said ok to the
ウイルスに感染した
wrong question so Android kind of
間違った質問なのでAndroidの種類
protects the skenes that kind of thing
skenesに そういうことを保護
because it's Android and it's gonna keep
それはAndroidだし、それは保つつもりだから
us a little bit safer so this device
私たちは少し安全なので、このデバイス
from oh and you might want to actually
ああから、あなたは実際にしたいことがあります
see I was doing this like Danah kind of
私がダナのようにやっていたのを見て
style waving and you didn't even get to
スタイルを振って、あなたも手に入れ ません でした
see my hand gestures
私の手のジェスチャーを見る
Kim tacks is a hardware creator and
Kim Tacksはハードウェアの作成者であり、
seller who has sent us this to review
私たち は、この見直しを送信した売り手
and we're just gonna get a quick look at
それでは、 ちょっと 見てみましょう 。
what this device gives us so there we go
この装置から得られるもの
it's a little bigger we can see right
それは我々 が正しく見る こと ができる 少し大きいです
out the gate then let's get it over the
ゲートから、その後のは、上でそれを取得してみましょう
packing here so this becomes an unboxing
これはアンボクシングになったので、ここでは梱包
video folks how do you like that little
ビデオの人々 あなたは その ちょっと が好きですか
bigger than the amazon firetv stick for
アマゾンfiretvスティック より も 大きい
sure let's get the cable off of there
確かにそこからケーブルを外しましょう
there we go there's the difference this
違いはあります
one looks more like a USB flash drive
USB フラッシュドライブの ように見える
this one looks more like a little itty
これはちょっと厄介なようです。
bitty computer kind of thing first
ちょっとしたコンピュータ類
things we notice okay first of all it
まず最初に大丈夫だ ということ
has a HDMI connection right there so
HDMI 接続 があります
that's gonna plug right into your TV or
それは 右の あなたのテレビ に つもり プラグ のです か
a little extension core
少し拡張 コア
which I presume is gonna be in the box
私は 箱に入れる つもりです
we'll take a look but it does have SD
私たちは見てみるでしょうが、それはSDを持っていますか
card reader that's lacking on the the
欠け て いるカードリーダー
amazon firetv stick that card reader
アマゾンfiretvスティックそのカードリーダー
will only go up to 32 gigs though
32ギグまでしか行かないだろう
according to the specifications which
これは仕様 に従って
little disappointing to be honest with
正直に言うと少しがっかり
you we've got a power Inlet and then
あなたは我々に パワー インレット を持っています そしてそれから
we've got two USB ports so we've got USB
USBポートが2つあるので USBがあります
3 right here this big one the full-size
ここ3 このフルサイズフルサイズ
is USB 3 and then we've got a USB to
USB 3です そしてそれから私達はにUSB を持っています
micro which is going to allow us to
私たちを可能にしようとしているマイクロ
plug-in peripherals so the side one is
周辺機器のプラグイン
just for providing 5 volts power to the
に5ボルトの電力を供給するためだけに
device now what's this red thing on the
今すぐデバイス上のこの赤いものは何ですか
side I mentioned about my desire to have
私の欲望について述べた側
better Wi-Fi and this one includes a
より良いWi-Fiとこれは含まれています
little bit of a signal boosting antenna
信号増強アンテナのほんの少し
that's gonna hang off the back of our TV
それ は私たちの テレビの 後ろにぶら下がるつもりです
there and give us better Wi-Fi so let's
もっと良いWi-Fiを提供しましょう
look at the specifications here just a
ここで仕様を見てください
little bit first of all the CPU is a
すべてのCPUの少し最初に
rockchip rk3288 so that's a 4 quart quad
それは 4クォートクワッドです
core
コア
yep that's the cortex a53 and it goes up
うんそれは皮質A53であり、上がる
to 1.5 3 gigahertz so for the form
1.5 3ギガヘルツな ので
factor it's pretty good I think that's
要因、それは私は それがだ と思うかなり良いです
pretty pretty impressive and we'll see
かなりかなり印象的です
if it generates any Heat I haven't
もしそれが熱 を発生させたら
notice any in my preliminary test GPU so
私の予備テストの GPUに 何か気づい た
the video output of this is with a
このビデオ出力はです
Mallee 450 MP 2 and that has OpenGL
マリー450 MP 2とそれは OpenGL を持っ ている
it's got 4k video output up to 60 frames
最大60フレームの 4k ビデオ出力
per second so right there blast the
毎秒とてもそう そこに 爆風
Raspberry Pi over the water okay so
ラズベリーパイの水に大丈夫そう
we've got pretty good video output at 60
60でかなり良いビデオ出力を得ました
frames a second in 4k 2k 1080p 720p I
4k 2k 1080p 720p Iで1秒のフレーム数
presume
推定する
but you plug this into your TV and boom
しかし、あなたはあなたのテレビとブームにこれを差し込みます
you've got instant access at up to 4k
あなたは4K までに 瞬時にアクセスを持っています
resolutions right 2 gigs of RAM inbuilt
2ギグのRAM内蔵解像度
16 gigabytes of storage there's also an
16ギガバイトのストレージ
8 gigabyte version as well so that's
8ギガバイト版 もそう です
like for your apps that you install but
あなたがインストールしたアプリのように
remember we've got a 32 gig SD card slot
32ギガSDカードスロットを持っていることを覚えておいてください
so I can increase that by up to 32 gigs
だから私は32ギグまでそれを増やすことができます
again I hear manufacturers saying hey
製造元がやあと言うのをもう一度
it'll support up to 32 gigs and then I
それは32ギグまでサポートし、 その後私は
stick a 128 in it and it works so so the
その中に128を貼り付けると、それはとてもうまくいきます
specifications say 32 maybe yeah
指定は32 多分そう言う
try something bigger 32 is pretty low
もっと大きい値を試してください32はかなり低いです
for today's absolutely specked so I kind
今日は絶対に斑点があるので私は親切
of when I read that in the
私がそれを読んだ時の
specifications it was like so kin tax we
それはそう親族 税の 我々のようだった仕様
want to up that a little bit now could
もうちょっと上げたい
that just simply be because if you have
それ は単に あなたが持っているからという理由 だけで ある
a say you put a 128 in there it's yeah
あなたは、それはそうだ 、そこに128を入れて言います
full of data that it bogs down the
それが浪費するデータでいっぱい
processing of it good though I don't see
見え ないけど加工はいい
how because it's storage right right so
それは正しいストレージだからどうやって
it's the storage system of the like a
それはのようなストレージシステムです
file system so basically the device is a
ファイルシステムなので基本的にはデバイスは
Linux device that sees that as a second
秒としてそれを見ているLinuxデバイス
storage medium that you can save photos
写真を保存できる記憶媒体
to save apps to save app data to but
アプリデータを保存するアプリを保存する
then again with something like this do
それからこのような何かで再び
you really need more than that you're
あなたが本当に必要としている以上のものが本当に必要です
not going to be downloading huge
巨大 に ダウンロードする つもりはない
applications I mean that because it's
アプリケーション私はそれだからということを意味します
not a computer third it's a TV set-top
コンピュータではなく、 テレビのセットトップです。
box that allows you to watch YouTube and
YouTubeを見ることができるボックス
streaming video platforms presumably
ストリーミングビデオプラットフォーム
category-five technology TV exactly
まさにカテゴリー5技術テレビ
otherwise out the window and so you
それ以外の場合は窓の外とあなたが
don't really I don't think need an
本当に 必要とは思わない
astronomical amount of space now do keep
天文学的なスペースの量は今保つ
in mind though USB 3 so if I wanted to
USB 3でも そうしたいのなら
you could plug in an external hard drive
あなたは外付けハードドライブを接続することができます
right power it with external power to
への 外部 電源 と右のパワーを
they don't want to power it off of this
彼らはこれからそれをオフにしたくない
and you're gonna have full speed access
あなたはフルスピードでアクセスするつもりです
to that hard drive that's cool that's at
そのハードドライブにかっこいい
times really good times Jeff really good
本当に良い時ジェフ本当に良い時
times Wi-Fi I mentioned okay so it's got
倍Wi-Fi私は大丈夫だと言ったので、それは持っている
2.4 gigahertz you know to 11 which is
2.4ギガヘルツあなたが知っている11に11
BGN and it has 5 gigahertz Wi-Fi as well
BGNとそれは 5ギガヘルツのWi-Fiも持っています
so you've got the BGN AC and Bluetooth
だからあなたはBGN ACと Bluetoothを持っている
4.1 so it's not Bluetooth 5 but
4.1だからBluetooth 5ではなく
bluetooth 4.1 so if you wanted to use
あなた が使用し たい場合は、Bluetooth 4.1ので
wireless earbuds from jeebies right if
jeebies からワイヤレスイヤホン 右あれば
you want to use your wireless headphones
ワイヤレスヘッドホンを使いたい
from House of Marley then you're able to
House of Marleyから 、
do that with this device and listen to
このデバイスでそれをしてに耳を傾ける
your music listen to your shows
あなたの音楽 はあなたの番組を聴く
wirelessly which is kind of a bonus I
ワイヤレスでボーナスの一種です私
definitely like that but also the other
間違いなくそのようなだけでなく、他の
advantage to having inbuilt bluetooth is
作り付けの ブルートゥースを持つ利点は
a lot of keyboards like you get
あなたが得るようなキーボードがたくさん
something like what we use for our
私たちのため に 使うもののようなもの
teleprompter here this is a Bluetooth
ここでテレプロンプターこれはブルートゥースです
keyboard so with this I simply turn it
キーボードだからこれで私は単にそれを回す
on sync it to this and boom we pair it
これと同期させると ペアリングします
to this and now I've got a keyboard and
これ に 、今、私はキーボードを持っているし、
you can get a full-size Bluetooth
フルサイズのBluetoothを 入手できます
keyboard and mouse and get a combo unit
キーボードとマウスとコンボユニットを入手
and you're good to go
行っ てよかっ た
and it operates a lot more like a
そしてそれは、
computer we're gonna plug it in and see
私たちはそれを差し込むつもりだし見ているコンピュータ
how much like a computer in just a
コンピュータの中でどれだけ
couple moments time one kind of final
カップルの 瞬間 時間最終の一種
thing I'll say because this is portable
これは移植可能なので私が言うこと
and you think hey this is something that
そして、 あなた はちょっとこれが 何か だと思います
I could take with me when I travel right
私は私が 正しく 旅行するとき私を 連れて行くことができ ました
yes and you could because it's HDMI you
はい、 あなたは それがあなたのHDMIだから 可能性があり ます
can plug it into the hotel TV and now
ホテルのテレビ に 、今 、それをプラグインすることができます
you've got because they provide Wi-Fi
あなたは彼らが Wi-Fi を提供するので持っている
and I've got YouTube Netflix whatever
そして 私は、YouTube Netflixのを持っているものは何でも
else the USB port supports a dongle from
さもなければUSB港は から のドングル を 支えます
your ISP so cool like a cellular dongle
携帯ドングルの ようにあなたのISPはとてもクール
now with a like the that with this stick
今 この棒でそれのように
here and then the like I don't know if
ここに そして それから私が知らないようなもの
they call it like a rocket hub or
彼らはそれをロケットハブのように呼ぶか
whatever from your ISP like a cellular
携帯電話のようにあなたのISPから何でも
internet that you plug into this now it
これで 今 接続するインターネット
provides its own internet so just
独自のインターネットを提供しています
awesome you don't even need Wi-Fi at
あなたもWi-Fi を 必要としない素晴らしい
that point perfect for the cottage all
コテージにぴったりのポイント
right so let's let's actually let's get
それでは実際に やってみましょう
finally into the box and see what else
最後に箱に入って、 他に 何があるか見る
we've got here because I want to plug it
私はそれを差し込みたいので ここに持っています
in for you while there's still time okay
まだ大丈夫な時間があるうちにあなたのために
yeah okay well what do we got what do we
ええ大丈夫よく 私たちは何を私たちは何を得た
got okay let's get that aside we've got
大丈夫になった
USB cable presumably for power we've got
私達が持っている電力用の USB ケーブル
a little oh look at that USB micro -
ちょっとああ、そのUSB マイクロを 見て -
full sized USB - so that's going to
フルサイズのUSB  - だからそれは
allow us to plug in standard sized
私たちは、 標準サイズのプラグインする こと が できます
peripherals to the micro port on the
のマイクロポートへの周辺機器
device that's good we've got a power
私たちは力を持っています
adapter this is a 2 amp 5 volt adapter
アダプタこれは 2アンペア 5ボルトのアダプタです。
USB micro and we've got that little HDMI
USBマイクロと私たちはその小さなHDMIを持っています
extension cord which makes it simply
簡単にする延長コード
easier for us to plug into the back of
私たちはの 背面に差し込むしやすいです
our TV because maybe maybe maybe that's
私達のテレビ
not gonna yeah if it's too close or
近すぎてもそうじゃない
whatever it may not plug directly into
直接接続できないものは何でも
the TV or maybe there's other
テレビか多分他がある
peripherals around so this gives you a
周辺機器なのでこれはあなたに
cable that you can kind of hang it or
あなたが一種の それ を掛ける こと ができるケーブルまたは
you know double-sided tape it to the
あなたは それをに両面テープを知っ ている
back of your TV it's that kind of thing
あなたのテレビの 後ろに それはそのようなものです
should we plug this in and see how she
私たちはこれを接続して彼女がどのように見るかを見るべきです
works all right so it's unanimous well
それは大丈夫ですので全会一致です
technically I didn't know what I was
技術的に私は自分が何であるかわからなかった
gonna say no just to be smart oh come on
ああに来るつもりはスマートであることを何も言わないだけ
if we looked at it but we're not gonna
私たちがそれを見たが、私たちはそうするつもりはない
actually look at it you're gonna see now
実際にあなたが 今 つもり 参照 していることを見て
how how complicated it is to set this up
これを設定するのがどれほど複雑か
right right cuz that's okay so two
それはので、2つ大丈夫だcuzの 右 右
cables okay so now down here I've got
ケーブルは大丈夫なので今 ここで 下 に持っています
I'm gonna grab an HDMI cable here I've
私はここでHDMIケーブルをつかむつもりです
got an HDMI jack that I can use here we
私たちはここで 私たち が使用できる HDMI ジャックを得た
go you guys talk amongst yourselves
あなたたちみんなの中で話をしに行きます
yeah this is gonna this looks like
うんこれはこの ようになる つもり です
something I could do well I got an HDMI
私は HDMIを 持ってうまく行うことができます何か
cable going out to my TV which is pretty
私のテレビに出ているケーブル は かわいいです
standard yeah and now an HDMI cable to
ええ標準となりましHDMIケーブル へ
your device and the only reason I have
あなたのデバイスと 私が持っている唯一の理由
that cable is because hey we're kind of
ちょっと私たちは一種 の だからそのケーブルがあります
far away from you watching in California
カリフォルニアから見てあなたから遠く離れて
right there we go it's plugged in all
すぐそこに行くそれはすべてに差し込まれている
right all right so let's switch over to
それでは上 に 切り替え ましょう
that screen and let's plug that in and
その画面とそれを接続しましょう
see what happens there's some juice
何 が起こる か見てくださいいくつかのジュースがあります
give it some instant all right let's see
すぐに見てみましょう
what comes up now I've got a Oh tea
今何が起きているか私は お茶を飲んでいる
that's some good processing power right
それはいくつかの良い処理能力です
there not bad good performance good
悪いパフォーマンスは良くない
performance so far I brought this with
これまでのパフォーマンス
me and it's got a USB dongle for a
私とそれ は USBドングル を 持っ てい ます
wireless keyboard so I'm simply gonna
ワイヤレスキーボードな ので、私は 単につもりです
plug this directly into the device I
これを直接デバイスに差し込みます
know you can't see but you can visualize
見えないが視覚化できることを知っている
yeah okay I'm gonna turn on that
ええ大丈夫私はそれをオンにするつもりだ
keyboard switch back to the screen for
キーボードが画面 に切り替えます
you and oh in Stan taneous access boom
あなたとああStanのtaneousアクセスブームで
chrome came with it what oh yeah
クロムはそれと一緒に来た
somebody's been testing this bad boy so
誰かがこの悪い男の子をテストしている
performance wise I notice that things
パフォーマンスの面で私は その こと に 気づく
are pretty zippy to open up and that's
開くことはかなりジッピーです、それはそれです
that nice Rockchip processor things
その素敵なロックチッププロセッサの もの
don't display absolutely perfectly on my
私には絶対に完璧に表示しないでください
website but not bad not bad
ウェブサイトだが 悪くない悪くない
oh you know what maybe it was just still
ああ、あなたはそれがたった今まだ何だったのか知っている
loading it does look pretty darn good
それをロードすることはかなり良く見えませんか？
scroll down a little bit here the one
ここを少し 下にスクロール
thing I don't like about these kinds of
私はこれらの種類について好きではないもの
devices is you've got to remember that
デバイスを覚えておく必要があります
this is Android it's built for a tablet
これはAndroidですそれはそれがタブレット用に構築されています
it's built for a phone so you notice
あなたは気づくので、それは携帯電話用に構築されています
there's no scroll bar I can't grab it
私はそれをつかむ こと はできませんスクロールバーはありません
like a computer and just oh man I'm
コンピュータ と 私は ちょうどああ 男のように
flicking with my finger so that means
指でフリックすると
clicking the mouse is scrolling clicking
マウスをクリックすると スクロールします
yeah now scrolling so it's a little bit
ええ、今スクロールしている のでちょっとだけ
of a different experience you got to get
あなたが得るために得た別の経験の
used to
のに使われます
that but it's not that bad and certainly
それはそれほど悪いことではなく、確かに
performance wise seems pretty good so
パフォーマンスに関して はかなり良いようです
I'm clicking on a video here and I click
私はここでビデオをクリックしていますそして私はクリックします
and pull up and click and pull not not
そして引き上げてクリックして引き出さない
the best UX but that's not that's
最高のUXです が、そうではありません
android yeah okay I'm gonna hit play and
アンドロイドええ大丈夫だよ私は プレイ を 打つつもり だ と
load times they're all those quick nice
ロード時間それらはすべてすばやく いいです
quick and nice shirt I'm wearing I know
私が着ている私が知っている私が着ているすばやくていいシャツ
right so one of the things that is
そう そういう ことの 一つ
important to me because this is going to
これはに なる ので私にとって重要
be a set-top device is you know full
セットトップ端末になる
screen video is there is it good is the
スクリーンビデオは、 それが良い です そこです
framerate good and it looks fantastic
良いフレームレート、それは素晴らしいですね
that's some pretty clean video I'm
これはかなりきれいなビデオ です
pretty impressed by that so this is just
きれいなので、これは ちょうど ある ことに感銘を受け
off of our website category five dot TV
私達のウェブサイトの部門から離れて5 点TV
via YouTube that kind of stuff
YouTubeを介してそのようなもの
it looks pretty good and it's flying out
それはかなりよさそうだし、 飛び出している
of the box now keep in mind I did plug
ボックスの説明今私はプラグをしたことを覚えておいてください
it in I went to two websites I tried a
それで私は私が試した2つのウェブサイトに行きました
couple of different things but I didn't
異なる こと がいくつかあります が 、私はしませんでした
I didn't install any drivers or anything
ドライバなど何もインストールしなかった
like that let's head on over directly to
そのようなものだが、 直接上に頭みましょう
YouTube which because I've got my my
私の持っているのでYouTube
stuff like my account in it wanted to
私のアカウントのようなもの がしたかった
log me in first right and you notice I
私の最初の権利をログインしてください、 あなたは私に気づく
used to work with Ellie I before they
以前はEllie Iと一緒に仕事をしていました
went out of business and so they wanted
事業の 出て行ったので 、 彼らが望んでいました
me to log in as them sad day sad day
私はそれらの悲しい日悲しい日でログイン します
okay so this is YouTube it looks pretty
大丈夫ですので、これはYouTubeですそれはきれいに見えます
darn good
気味が悪い
mmm-hmm so again you've got to get used
mmm-hmmなので、もう一度 慣れる 必要があります
to this kind of clicking and scrolling
クリックやスクロール の この種に
action looks like I kind of got a all I
アクションは私が一種のすべて私を手に入れたように見えます
got to use the keyboard to maneuver now
今すぐ操縦するためにキーボードを使うように なった
I will get that sometimes doesn't matter
私は時々 問題に ならないと思うよ
what you're using I mean our Android box
あなたが使っているのは私たちのAndroidボックスを意味します
at home yeah same deal I mean we have I
家でも同じ取引私たちは私を持っているという意味
think the same remote oh yeah so the
同じリモート だと思う
quality the clarity is brilliant I don't
透明度が素晴らしい品質私はしない
know how to turn it off so that I can
私ができるようにそれをオフに する方法を知っている
not breach copyright but there you go I
著作権侵害ではありませんが、私はそこに行きます
mean so that's working really a treat a
そのためには 、実際に御馳走aを 働い て いる 意味
couple of the features that we want to
私たちがしたい機能のカップル
look at okay if I go into all apps
私は すべてのアプリ に入るなら大丈夫を 見て
I did try installing game but I couldn't
私はゲームをインストールしようとしましたが、できませんでした
get it working I'm not too sure what's
うまくいくかどうか私にはわかりません
going on there but I did notice that
そこに行くが 、私はそれに 気づいた
we've got things pre-built in like Wi-Fi
Wi-Fiのようなものがあらかじめ組み込まれています
display and I did a quick pair
ディスプレイと私は簡単なペアをしました
to my smartphone and instantaneously I
私のスマートフォンに そして瞬時に私は
had access to my phone really yeah I
私は、ええ 、本当に私の携帯電話 へのアクセスを持っていました
wanted to show you this because
これを見せたかった
sometimes Web Apps maybe maybe I can't
時々 Webアプリは 多分私はできないかもしれません
get Netflix working on there because
Netflixがそこで動作するようにする
it's a Chinese device and Netflix is
それは中国の機器であり、Netflixは
pretty particular about the the
についてかなり詳しく
geolocation of their viewers kind of
その視聴者の地理的位置の種類の
thing so maybe I want to bring up
なので私は育てたい
Netflix on here just as an example right
ちょうど例としてここにNetflix
or maybe I want to bring up I watch the
または多分 私は 私が 見 て育てたいのです が
countdown every New Year's on my phone
私の電話では1年ごとのカウントダウン
and that gives me a chance to now cast
そして それは 私 に今キャスト するチャンス を 与え ます
it to the device so let's actually do
それをデバイスにする ので、実際にやろう
that I'm just I brought up miracast on
私は ちょうど 私が ミラキャスト を育て た
my computer on my phone here and I'm
ここに私の電話で私のコンピュータと私は
gonna click on my phone which it already
私の携帯電話をクリックしてください
detected impaired and hit okay and oh
障害を検出し、大丈夫をヒットし、ああ
it's already connecting and there we go
それはすでにつながっています
Wow so now I'm actually in my phone so
うわーだから今私は実際に 私の電話にいるので
if I bring up like I guess YouTube on my
私が YouTubeで私が推測するように私が育てれ ば
phone now what's that look like so there
電話今それがそこにあるように見えるものは何ですか
we go Wow right so now if I turn my
私は自分の向きを変えれば今すぐにすごい
phone sideways I'm physically turning it
横に電話をかけている
sideways there it's all just it adjusts
横にそれは それが調整するだけです
it itself and this is done now keep in
それ自体で、これは今続けて行われます
mind this is done completely wirelessly
これは 完全にワイヤレス で行われます
so what I'm seeing on the screen here is
画面に表示されるのは
being cast to the device through my
私を通してデバイスにキャストされている
Wi-Fi network I didn't have to sinful
Wi-Fiネットワーク私は罪を犯す必要はありませんでした
didn't even have to set anything up it
何も設定する必要はありませんでした
was so super simple so I think there's
その超 簡単だったので、私はそこだと思います
some really good value in that on its
その上でいくつかの本当に良い値
own and so then if I click on my vlog
自分の ブログ をクリックし たら
from today for example for patrons
今日から、例えば後援者のために
there's a there's some latency there for
いくらかの待ち時間 があります
sure that maybe my network I don't know
たぶん私のネットワークがわからない
but still the point is it's kind of it
それでもポイントはそれがそのようなものです
was warming up yeah it's kind of you
ウォーミングアップしていた
know how you tube will kind of crap down
あなたのチューブがどのようにがらくたをするのか知っている
the quality if if your bandwidth is not
あなたの帯域幅が そうで なければ品質
very good right so but it works it works
非常に良いそうだけど、うまくいく
great there you go so well done okay so
素晴らしいそこに行くあなたはとてもうまく行った
now I'm stuck I can't bring you back so
今私はあなたを とても 戻すことはできませんこだわっています
I've got to actually turn off miracast
私は実際に miracastをオフ に するんです
in order to get back there we go okay
そこに戻るために私達は 大丈夫 行きます
now I'm back there I can escape back
今私は戻って 逃げることができる そこ に戻ってきた
right and there's our menu a couple of
そうですね、 私たちのメニュー はいくつかあります。
other quick things here we've got the
ここで私たちが持っている他の簡単なこと
Play Store obviously our KMC looks a
Playストアは明らかに私たちの KMCは
like you know like XBMC or Kodi that
あなたのようなことを XBMCや コディ のように知っています
kind of thing yeah so that comes pre
そういうことそうなんですよ
built in you can add your channels and
あなたに組み込まれて あなたのチャンネルを追加する ことが できます
to get out of that it's the power button
それから抜け出すには、電源ボタンです
over here so definitely worth checking
ここをチェックする価値がある ので間違いなく
out
でる
if you're looking for a set-top box this
セットトップボックスを探しているなら これ
is obviously like a little tiny thing
明らかに小さい ことの ような ものです
the Wi-Fi on it is spectacular is really
その上のWi-Fiは壮観です
really good Wi-Fi at my house no latency
私の家では本当に良いWi-Fi は 待ち時間なし
no problem running YouTube so watching
YouTubeを起動しても問題ありません。
YouTube videos that's really all we need
YouTubeのビデオ が本当に必要なものすべて
it for right and it works perfectly it
それは正しいのためにそれはそれが完璧に動作します
doesn't have an accelerometer like your
あなたのような加速度計を持っていません
phone does so if games require that you
ゲームがあなたにそれを要求するならば、電話はそうします
be able to turn the phone like this
このように電話を回すことができる
obviously it's not going to work but
明らかにうまくいきませんが
games I presume like Angry Birds that
Angry Birdsが好きなゲーム
kind of stuff rattle or house driven you
ガラガラとか家のようなもの
can you can do that so yeah check that
あなたはとても ええ ことを 確認することを行うことができますすることができます
out it's cat five dot TV slash r33
それの 猫 5つのドット のテレビスラッシュR33 アウト
because that's the Kintex r33 Android TV
それはKintex r33 Android TV だから
stick checks today good times all right
スティックチェック今日良い時間大丈夫
well uh well uh well gonna take a break
ええともええとも休憩を取ります
I think we probably should better take a
私たちはおそらく より良い服用する べきだと思います
break yeah responses well you got to pay
ええ破る応答 だけでなく、あなたが支払うことになりました
the bills
請求書
maybe watch this short what's kind of
これをちょっと見てみましょう
Jeff so coming up we're gonna help you
ジェフが出てくるのでお手伝いします
sleep with a sleeping mask it's got a
寝ているマスクで眠る
twist did you know what that twist is I
ねじれあなたはそのねじれが私が何であるか知っていましたか
have a feeling we're gonna find out
私たちが見つけるつもりだ気がする
that's it that's right it's got built-in
そうです、そのこと だ 、それは内蔵の持っています
audio don't go anywhere
オーディオはどこにも行かない
[Music]
[音楽]
[Applause]
[拍手]
whether you shop on ThinkGeek gearbest
ThinkGeekギアベストで買い物をするかどうか
B&amp;H photo video eBay or Amazon or even
B&amp;Hの写真ビデオのeBayやAmazon、さらには
if you want a free trial up audible
無料試用版を聞きたい場合
you'll find the best deals and support
あなたは最高のお得な情報やサポートを見つけることができます
the shows we produce by simply visiting
我々 が単に 訪れることによって作り出すショー
the shopping sites you already frequent
あなたがすでに頻繁に訪れるショッピングサイト
by using the links on our website visit
当社のウェブサイト訪問のリンクを使用して、
category-five TV slash partners for the
のためのカテゴリ5 TVスラッシュパートナー
full and ever-growing list and help us
フルと増え続けるリスト と私たちを助けます
create more free content like this show
この 番組の ように 無料で コンテンツを作成する
thank you for shopping with our partners
私たちのパートナー と一緒に買い物をし て くれてありがとう
and thank you for watching welcome back
バック歓迎を見ていただきありがとうございます
we are about to put you to sleep and
私たちはあなたを眠らせようとしています
make it quite enjoyable ah that's gonna
それは非常に楽しいああそれをするつもりだ
be one of those shows a where we put
それらの 一つであることは、我々は置く場所 を示します
them to sleep
彼らは寝る
exactly yeah no we are going to be
まさにそうではありませ ん
reviewing a sleeping mask with some
いくつかの睡眠のマスクを見直す
audio components to it okay
それへのオーディオコンポーネント大丈夫
so I guess the first question I have to
だから私は私が し なければならない最初の質問を推測
ask is why would you want audio
なぜオーディオ が 欲しいですか
components of sleeping masks if you're
眠っている マスクの 構成要素
going to be sleeping this is what I
これは私 が眠っ ていることです
normally wear when I'm sleep and Jeff
普段は眠っているときに着てジェフ
really yeah well and I was going to say
本当にうん 、私は言うつもりだった
if you ask my wife she'd say it's
私の妻に聞いたら彼女はそれを言うだろう
because I snore do you have tinnitus I
私はいびきをかくので、あなたは 耳鳴りを 持っています I
do ah oh my gosh so bad so you hear the
ああああ私のgoshは とても悪い ので、あなたが聞く の
ringing all the time and it's like my
いつも鳴っていて、それは私のようです
wife doesn't understand that the fan is
妻はファンが
not because it's hot out it's because I
私ので、それはだ からそれは暑いではないので、
need the noise so it's true I I sleep
それは本当の II睡眠 ですので 、ノイズが必要です
with these in my ear Jeff okay Sasha
私の耳にこれらを使ってJeff 大丈夫 Sasha
I've found a brand of earbuds that are
あるブランド の イヤホン を 見つけました
flat so that I can lay on my side and it
私は私の側にそれを置くことができるように平ら
doesn't hurt my ears right right but
耳を痛めないように正しい
they break yeah I buy them in bulk you
彼らはええ 私はそれら をまとめてあなた を買う
can buy bags of them on Amazon for
のためにアマゾンでそれらのバッグを購入することができます
twenty to twenty bucks for twenty a year
20 年 20〜20ドル
buds but they break all the time and I
芽は出ますが、いつも壊れています
you know I feel bad to scrap them I cut
あなたは私がそれらをスクラップするのが悪いと感じるのを知っています
the cables off and I recycle them and
ケーブルを外して、リサイクルして
everything else not ideal right why do I
他のすべては理想的ではありません
do that
それをする
I listen I learn I sleep better because
私はよく眠ることを学びます
I have audio that's you
あなたの音声があります
maybe it's nature sounds sometimes it's
多分それは、時には それはだ 聞こえる自然です
nature's hands for me sometimes it's
私のための自然の手
podcasts maybe it's an audiobook what do
ポッドキャスト多分それは 何を するのオーディオブック です
you do you ever listen to things at
あなたは今までに物事を聴いていますか
night
夜
believe it or not most of it is music if
それを信じるかどうかは音楽の大部分ではない
I ever music is it like gentle yes
私は今まで音楽は優しいそうですね
simply stuff no words yeah it's usually
単に言葉を詰め込む
like some sort of this stuff you hear
このようなものが好きです
when you have like massage so it's like
マッサージが好きなときに
it's a meditation thing like I'll call
私が呼ぶような瞑想的なものです
that like solitudes or maybe like I
孤独や私のようなもの
guess technically they call it like
技術的に彼らはそれを好きだと思います
new-age music when you know not
知らない時のニューエイジの音楽
technically it doesn't have to be New
技術的には新品である必要はありません
Age but you sometimes hear that kind of
年齢しかし、あなたは時々 の ようなものを聞きます
stuff with with like ambient birds and
周囲の鳥のように
things like that yeah I love nature
そのような ことええ私は 自然が 大好き
sounds I actually have a show called
私は実際に呼ばれるショーを持っているように聞こえます
immersive nature sounds where you can
没入型自然はあなたができるところに聞こえます
you can listen to nature in binaural 3d
バイノーラル3Dで自然を 聴くことができます
surround sound with just a standard pair
標準ペアでサラウンドサウンド
of headphones and to sleep with that
ヘッドフォンのそれと一緒に寝て
like a thunderstorm for example you've
例えば雷雨のように
got a 12 hour thunderstorm on on that
その上で12時間の雷雨を 得 ました
show where you can listen for 12 hours
12時間聴ける場所を表示する
it's just perfect for sleeping with or
それだけで寝るのに最適ですまたは
studying with that would be 12 hours of
それを研究することの 12時間になります
stress for my dog but it helps me to
私の犬のためのストレスが、それは私を助け
sleep it helps me to get my mind off
それ は私の心をオフにするの に 役立ちます 眠り ます
things as the main thing because I'm a
私はですので、主なものとして物事
very go-go-go guy I'm always programming
私はいつもプログラミングしている
I'm always coming up with inventions and
私はいつも発明を 思いついています
so when I go to bed it's like I need my
だから私が寝るときは私が必要としているようなものです
mind to declutter right so see things
正しく理解 するために、物事を見て
that's true
それは本当だ
okay so earbuds are not perfect what do
大丈夫ですので、イヤホンは完璧ではありません。
you use your but yeah yeah same thing
あなたはあなたのを使用します が、 ええ同じようなこと
same kind of deal and this seems like
同種の取引で、これは
it's new to you like you well I have a
それは私が持っているだけでなく 、あなたのようにあなたに新機能
white noise generator that sits beside
横にあるホワイトノイズ発生器
my bed okay
私のベッドは大丈夫
similar kind of thing yeah if your
似たようなことがあれば
husband hears that well yeah it's for
夫はよくええ、それがためだと聞きます
him okay
彼は大丈夫
so maybe if there so when I was single
私が独身だったときにそうかもしれないので
back before before I was married so many
私はとても結婚していた前に前に戻って
many years ago I had a speaker that was
何年も前に私はスピーカーだった
under my pillow and that would help me
私の枕の下に、 それは 私 を 助ける だろう
because that was under my pillow and I
それは私の枕と 私 の下にあったので、
could hear it but now being married for
それを聞くことができましたが、今結婚しています
as many years I can't do that because my
何年もの間、私はそれができません。
wife would go nuts for a while I knew
妻は 私が知っていたしばらく の 間 、 ナットを行くだろう
any wife yeah what we first like I
いずれの妻ええ私たち最初の I のような
always fell asleep to music when we
我々がいるときはいつも音楽に眠り込んでいた
first got married like if if a crick
最初の クリックの ように結婚した
passes gas my wife wakes up the fact
私の妻は事実を目覚めさせるガスを渡します
that I would normally sleep with music
私は通常音楽で眠るだろう
she was just like so of course she wins
彼女はちょうど 彼女が勝っもちろん のように、 のようでした
out so listening to a reenactment of The
の再現を 聞い て
Hobbit was not in the cards no
ホビットは カードにいませんでした
definitely not so I had to learn to fall
絶対にそうではないので私は転倒することを学ばなければならなかった
asleep with right that's when the ear
耳で眠るのはそのときに眠りにつく
ringing tinnitus comes in yeah it's
鳴っている耳鳴りはそうだね
thoughts start going so earbuds are not
思考は動き始めますのでイヤホンはそうではありません
perfect never liked them they're a
彼らが好きで完璧な
little uncomfortable then along comes
それから 少し 不快なそれから来る
cat5 TV slash mask you ready for this
cat5 TVスラッシュマスクあなたはこれの準備ができて
Jeff yes cuz I feel like we're we're
Jeff yes cuz私 たちは私たちだ という気 がします
like one with this right now I stash
これで 今のもののように私は隠します
this like that's weird yeah this is
これは変だね
something that I need it's not
必要なものでは ない
completely weird I want it's not
完全に奇妙で はない
completely weird it's it's so sweet
それはとても甘いです。
alright so first of all this is cap 5 TV
大丈夫な ので、まず最初にこれは キャップ5 TVです。
slash mask and it comes in a nice case
マスクをスラッシュし、それはいいケースに来る
it does look a lot like a doobies case
それは doobiesの場合と よく 似 ていますか
but it's not actually it's not a
それは実際にはそうではありません
charging case this is just a holding
充電ケースこれは ただの持ち株です
case Sasha you're doing some traveling
ケースサーシャあなたは旅行をしています
coming up so yes Dave and I are going
そうデイブと私は行きます
back to Newfoundland to usually sleep
通常眠る ためにニューファンドランド に戻る
with a mask when you're on a plane well
あなたがよく飛行機の上にいるとき、マスクで
this is what would work for me I don't
これは私のために 働くもの です私はしないでください
need I don't need a sleep mask and I
私は 睡眠マスクとIを必要としない 必要があります
don't need audio or anything in my home
私の家には オーディオなど 何も 必要ない
my home is my cocoon but when I'm in
私の家は私の繭です が、私がいるとき
public and needing some sleep yeah this
公衆といくつかの睡眠を必要とするそうこれ
is what I would and it's hard to sleep
私がすることであり、それ は眠り にくいです
on a plane I'd imagine so I've never
飛行機の中で私は想像すると思います
been a long enough flight but if ever
十分に長時間のフライトでしたが 、これまで であれば
going from like Canada to rail yeah and
カナダのように鉄道に行く
that was a long flight 107 half just the
それは長距離路線の107 分 だけだっ た
one jaunt over the ocean and it was
海の上を一突き
painful overnight because you got the oh
一晩中痛みを伴う
yeah the parents yelling at their kids I
ええ、両親は子供たちに叫んでいます
could use this to Newfoundland it's a
これをニューファンドランドに使うことができる
sleeping mask okay just a sleeping mask
寝ているマスク大丈夫 ちょうど寝ているマスク
right nice this side uh-huh uh-huh just
右 素敵なこちら側フンフン フンフンだけ
hold it on Jeff don't get ahead of
ジェフを手に入れよう
yourself so first of all the thing that
まず自分自身
I got to point out is that it is a
私が指摘したのは、それが
special type of velcro so if you feel
あなたが感じるならベルクロの特別なタイプなので
this it's not the kind that's gonna get
これは得るつもりの種類ではありません
caught on oh yeah yeah
ええええオハイオ州 でキャッチ
it's pretty that's very cool it's not
それはかなりクールだよそれはいないよ
gonna get caught or damaged but here we
巻き込まれたり破損したりするつもりですが、ここで私たちは
go so I'm gonna put that on like that
行くので私はそのようにそれを置くつもりだ
and now you see me so you know it's a
そして今、あなたは私に会います ので、あなたはそれが
sleeping mask right right with a twist
ひねりを加えた睡眠マスク
so this particular one let's get back
だからこの特定のもの は取り戻しましょう
here for un no that's that's wrong
ここではなしのためにそれは 間違っている
that's a beautiful little Android device
それは美しい小さな Android デバイスです
look at the back of here so we've got
ここの後ろを見てください。
stereo headphones built into the
に 内蔵されている ステレオヘッドホン
sleeping mask and here's the the inlet
眠っているマスクとここが入り口です
right here so in the case is a one and a
まさにここでそうである場合には1と
half meter cable I like that this is
ハーフメーターケーブルこれが好き
detached Jeff to be honest with you
あなたと正直になるようにJeffを切り離しました
because I always you know I damaged the
私はいつもあなたが知っているので、私は、損傷しました
cables because you roll over and you you
ロールオーバーして
damaged it so I've had this actually get
それを 損傷 したので、私はこれを実際に得てもらいました
pulled out a couple times and it still
数 回引き出したが、 それでもまだ
works just fine it's easy to eject which
うまく動作し ます
is a good thing because if I roll over
ロールオーバーすれば良いことです
it's not gonna get damaged right and it
それは 正しく 破損するつもりはない 、それはそれ
works quite well so there you go so it's
非常にうまく機能するので、そこに行くので、 それは
stereo audio built into a sleeping mask
スリーピングマスクに組み込まれたステレオオーディオ
okay hold on
わかったまってて
well no no before you do that I'm plug
あなたが する前に私はプラグを
it in you're gonna plug it in oh you got
それであなたはそれを差し込むつもりだあああなたが持っている
some like dubstep beats that you're
ダブステップのようなものはあなたがいることを打つ
hugging in okay so what what's gonna
大丈夫で抱き締めるので何が起こっているの
play it's an audio book an audio book
それはオーディオブックです オーディオブック
okay okay
大丈夫大丈夫
make it happen Jeff I'm waiting for it
それを実現するためにJeff
Jeff I just hit play okay turn it up
ジェフ私はちょうどプレーを打つ大丈夫それを上げる
okay yeah I can hear it turn it down a
大丈夫そう私はそれを断る聞くことができます
bit
ビット
it's blaring it's blaring he has a very
それは彼が非常に持っていることを非難しています
nice voice but it's David super fine
いい声だけどデビッドは超結構
yeah yeah too quiet you've muted it yes
あなたはそれをミュートにしました
there a little more
もう少しあり ます
I'll go for it turn it up yeah pump up
私はそれのために行きますそれはそれを上げるそれを上げるポンプ
the jam yeah okay okay perfect alright
ジャムええ大丈夫大丈夫完璧 大丈夫
you wanna try that on okay that's just
あなたはそれだけだ大丈夫 にそれを試してみたいです
gonna try that on there you go so there
あそこ でやってみるよ
is a Bluetooth model but I decided to go
はBluetoothモデルですが、私は行くことにしました
with the hardwired because I like that
私 はそれが好きだ からハードワイヤード で
it does not use batteries and have to
それは電池を使用しないし、しなければなりません
worry about it like running out of
が不足しているようにそれを心配
battery life while I'm sleeping what do
寝ている間の電池寿命
you think sash yeah it's David Suchet
あなたはサッシそうだと思うそれはデビッドスシェットだ
that guy's got an amazing voice here's a
あの 男は素晴らしい声をここに持っている
couple of things that I've noticed in
私が気づいたことのいくつかのこと
using this mask over the past couple of
過去の2、3回にわたってこのマスクを使用する
days sorry that I borrowed your
借りてごめんなさい
tested it here's the thing it's
それはここだことだテスト
comfortable yeah okay yes is it it is
快適そうはい 大丈夫 はい それはそれです
confidence comfort about its padded
そのパッド についての自信の慰め
feels good here Jeff you gotta try it
ここで気分が良い
because you're the guy who who needs one
あなたはそれを必要とする人だから
of these it is comfortable
これらのうちそれは快適です
yeah and I have a smaller head and it
ええと私は頭が小さいとそれ
was nice on me I also think if I wanted
私にはよかった私も ほしかったら私はまた 考える
to get into crime fighting career it
犯罪との闘いに入るために
would work for that just drill a hole
それの ために 働く だけで穴を開ける
through those holes in that music yeah
あの音楽の 穴を通して
you could have your own sounds and and
あなたはあなた 自身の音を 持つことができます
everything like soundtrack
サウンドトラックのようなすべてのもの
I think dubstep beats all of them cat5
私はダブステップが それら すべてを打つと思いますcat5
dot TV slash mask you know it's a simple
ドットTVスラッシュ マスクあなたはそれが簡単だと知っている
thing it's cheap it's it's affordable
それは安いですそれはそれが手頃な価格です
but it's well built it works well and
それはうまく構築されています
comfortable to it is quite comfortable I
それに快適快適な私
imagine you know we're all we're various
あなたは私たちがすべて私たちがさまざまであることを知っていると想像してください
shapes and sizes here and it seems to
形や 大きさ、ここで、それがいるようです
fit all of us I don't know if you'd ever
私たちの すべてにフィット私はあなたが今までにいたかどうかわからない
have any trouble with that fitting even
そのフィッティングに 問題があっ ても
if you had a really big noggin there's
あなたは本当に大きな ノギンを持っている場合があります
there's I wonder if you had a huge head
頭が大きいのかしら
if the earphones would maybe be too far
イヤホンが多すぎるかも
for example possibly but I feel like the
例えば多分しかし私はのように感じます
majority of head girth would be this not
頭囲の大部分はこれで はない でしょう
between the eyes and the ears maybe well
目と耳の 間
it's pretty standard depth yeah and I
それはええ 、かなり標準の深さだと私
mean those are big ear pieces so I mean
これらは大きな耳の部分ですので私は意味
even if your ears were back and forth
あなたの耳が 前後にあっても
you've probably got like inch
あなたはおそらくインチのようになった
inch-and-a-half play at least so it's
少なくとも0.5インチプレーするので
pretty good there you go very cool check
なかなかいいですね
it out cat 5 TV slash mask the show cost
それは猫5 テレビスラッシュマスクショーコスト
me money Ravi oh do you like that yeah
私のお金ラヴィああ あなたはそのように好き です か
but the show also informs that's right
ショーはまた正しいことを知らせます
yes yes so what's going on in the news
はいはいそうニュース で何が起こっているのか
room do you know I don't have a clue
部屋は 私は手掛かりを持っていない 知ってい ます
that's that's the real truth of the
それが本当の真実です
matter all right here are the stories
ここで大丈夫なのはストーリーです
were covering this week in the category
今週のカテゴリーでカバーしていた
5 TV newsroom Microsoft is
5 テレビニュースルームマイクロソフトは
acquiring github the FBI is advising
FBIが助言しているgithubを取得する
users of consumer grade router routers
消費者向けルータールーターのユーザー
and network attached storage devices to
およびネットワーク接続ストレージデバイス
reboot them as soon as possible to
できるだけ早くにそれらを再起動します
counter Russian engineered malware that
ロシアが設計したマルウェア
has infected hundreds of thousands of
何十万もの感染者
Services devices how's the contacts
デバイスに サービスを提供 する
tonight's ash just asking I just want to
今夜の灰 はただ欲しいだけ
know can we increase the font size Apple
フォントサイズを大きくする ことができますか。
I'm okay previewed a variety of security
さまざまなセキュリティをプレビューしても大丈夫です
and privacy features it plans to add to
追加予定のプライバシー機能
me to Mac OS and iOS operating systems
私 はMac OS およびiOSのオペレーティング・システム に
including encrypted FaceTime group calls
暗号化されたFaceTimeグループ通話を含む
password management tools and camera and
パスワード管理ツールとカメラ
microphone protections asus has staged
asus が上演したマイクの保護
its annual Computex keynotes and shown
毎年恒例 のComputexの基調講演 と示します
off a laptop with dual screens but it's
二重スクリーンのあるラップトップでは
not at all what you're imagining these
すべてではないあなたは これらを 想像しているもの
stories are coming right up don't go
物語はすぐに来ていない行かないで
anywhere
どこでも
Jeff Westen Java
ジェフ ウェステンジャワ
you're building a brand-new beautiful
あなたは真新しい美しいを構築しています
website what
ウェブサイト何
are you alright you're terrible actor
あなたは大丈夫ですあなたはひどい俳優です
what this whereat thing comes into play
何このwhereat 事が 戦場 に出ました
you're supposed to act okay are you
あなたは大丈夫 あなたが 行動することになっています
building a really cool website are you
本当にクールなWebサイトを構築するのはあなたです
building a really cool website just
本当にクールなWebサイトを構築する
because Jeff is confused doesn't mean
ジェフは混乱している ので、 意味する ものではありません
you have to be visit cap five dot TV
あなたはキャップ 5ドットテレビを 訪問する必要があります
slash DreamHost to sign up for unlimited
DreamHost を スラッシュ して無制限にサインアップ
web hosting for your website with
あなたのウェブサイトのためのウェブホスティング
unlimited email accounts MySQL databases
無制限の電子メール アカウントMySQLデータベース
the latest version of PHP WordPress and
PHP WordPressの 最新バージョン
more and even a free domain name
もっと無料のドメイン名
registration it's less than six dollars
登録は6ドル未満です
per month so sign up today cat five dot
1ヶ月あたりのために 今日の サインアップ 猫5ドット
TV slash dream host this is the category
テレビスラッシュドリームホストこれはカテゴリです
five dot TV newsroom covering the week's
今週の 5ドットテレビ ニュースルーム
top tech stories with a slight linux
ちょっとしたlinuxを使ったトップテックストーリー
glass i'm satiric menon here the top
ガラス 私はここに風刺のメノンだ
stories were following this week
今週の物語
Microsoft is this aquire in github after
マイクロソフトはこの後githubで買収しました
reports emerged that the software giant
ソフトウェアの巨人が
was in talks to acquire github Microsoft
マイクロソフトgithubを買収するために協議中だった
is making it official on Monday github
月曜日のgithub で 正式になりました
was last valued at 2 billion dollars
最後の 20 億ドル と評価されました
back in 2015 and Microsoft is paying 7.5
2015年に戻ってマイクロソフトは7.5を支払っている
billion in stock for the company in a
会社のための10億ドルの株式
deal that should close later this year
今年後半に終了するはずの取引
github is a large code repository that
githubは大きなコードリポジトリ です。
has become very popular with the
と 非常に人気になっています
developers and companies hosting entire
全体をホストする開発者および企業
projects documentation and code Apple
プロジェクトのドキュメントとコードApple
Amazon Google and many other big tech
Amazon Googleおよび 他の多くのビッグ テック
tech companies use github there are 85
ハイテク企業は85があるgithubを使用
million repositories hosted on github
githubでホストされている100万のリポジトリ
github and 28 million developers
githubと2800万人の開発者
contribute to them github will now be
彼らに貢献githubは今になります
led by CEO and nod Freedman who will
CEOとうなずきFreedmanが率いる
report to Microsoft cloud and all and
マイクロソフトのクラウドに報告し、すべての
chief Scott Guthrie github CEO and
Scott Guthrie githubの最高経営責任者（CEO）と
co-founder Chris Warren Warren therethe
共同創設者クリスウォーレンウォーレンがそこに
will now become a technical fellow at
でテクニカルフェローになります
Microsoft also reporting to Guthrie it's
マイクロソフトもガスリーに報告しています
easy to imagine why Microsoft would want
Microsoft が なぜ 望んでいるのか想像しやすい
to acquire github Microsoft killed its
githubを買収するためにMicrosoftは 殺害した
own github competitor codeplex in
独自のgithub競合他社のコードプレックス
December and is now the top contributor
12月になり、現在はトップ寄稿者
to github Microsoft now has more than
Microsoftにgithubするために今以上の ものがあります
1,000 employees actively pushing code to
1000人の従業員が積極的に コードを推進しています
github repositories Microsoft has
マイクロソフトのgithubリポジトリ
struggle
闘争
old with the developer love for years
何年もの間開発者の愛をこめて古い
and it's a big part of the reasons when
それはときの理由の大きな部分です
those failed and its univer windows
失敗したものとその ユニバースウィンドウ
phone failed and it's Universal windows
電話が失敗し、それはユニバーサル ウィンドウズです
apps platform hasn't taken off the
アプリプラットフォームはオフになっていません
question around this acquisition will be
この買収に関する質問は
what Windows does with github github in
Windowsはgithubののgithubの中で何をしますか
the future Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella
未来のマイクロソフトCEO、Satya Nadella
says we are committed to being stewards
私たちはスチュワードになることを約束しています
of the github community which will
その意志 githubのコミュニティの
retain its developer first a toast
開発者を最初 に乾杯させる
operate independently and remain an open
独立して運営し、 オープンなまま
platform we will always listen to
私たちがいつも耳にしているプラットフォーム
developer feedback and invest in both
開発者からのフィードバックと投資
fundamentals and new capabilities this
基礎と新 機能
was an interesting story did not see
おもしろい話でしたが見えませんでした
that coming no what no I mean when when
いつ 来たん だ
it was first announced I was like really
それは私が本当に好きだった最初に発表されました
of all the people to buy it
それを買うため にすべて の人々の
Microsoft because Microsoft I mean
マイクロソフトだからMicrosoft
granted I'm not a huge Microsoft fan but
Microsoftの大ファンで は ないが
they're known for taking things and
彼らは物 を取る ことで知られています
absorbing them and killing the life out
それらを吸収して命を殺す
of it any do you have an example just
それのどれでもあなたは ちょうど例 を持っていますか
everything just no but I mean anytime
すべてのこと だけでなく、私は いつでも 意味
Microsoft has acquired stuff I feel like
マイクロソフトは私が気に入ったものを入手しました
there's always been a community support
コミュニティサポートが常にありました
around whatever it might have been a I'm
それが私だったかもしれないものは何でも
blanking on things right now but then
今のことにブランクが、その後
Microsoft takes over and you get that
マイクロソフトが引き継ぎ、あなたはそれを手に入れました
major corporate feel but have they taken
主要な企業の雰囲気
a more open source approach as of late
最近のオープンソースアプローチ
like the past say three years that have
過去と同じように3年間
we kind of got that impression that I
私たちはそのような印象を 持っています
don't think so
そうは思わない
no no I mean when I switched over to
いいえ、私は私がに切り替えたときに意味します
Windows 10 on my home PC
私の自宅のPCの Windows 10
I don't feel who knows well not with
私は誰と 一緒に よく知っているとは思わない
their not with their software but with
彼らのソフトウェアではなく
their approach to the developer channels
開発者チャネルへの彼らのアプローチ
and things like that I guess a little
そして私は 少し 推測する ようなもの
bit but I mean this is completely open
少しでもこれは完全に開いているという意味
so I mean that's a great thing about
だから私はそれが 素晴らしいことだということ です
github is is it's totally open source
github は 完全に オープンソースです
right and so the idea that attribute
そうそしてその 考え その属性
their own code seems so positive
彼ら自身のコードはとてもポジティブに見えます
Microsoft's gonna win it I really oh hey
マイクロソフトが勝つつもりだよ
how can you how can you ruin something
どうやってあなたはどうやって あなたは 何か を台無しに することができ ます
that's so big though to see your job but
それはあなたの仕事を見て てもとても大きいですが、
as long as they don't change it did the
変更 しない 限り 、
fundamental underlying and they say that
根本的な基礎と彼らはそれを言う
they're keeping that open
彼らはそれを開いたままにしています
at those of how it works how it operates
それがどのように動作するかをどのように動作するかのそれらの
and the the underlying mindset of of
そしてその根底にある考え方
github because if if you create a piece
githubあなたが作品を作成した場合
of software and publish it to github now
ソフトウェアをダウンロードして 今すぐ githubに公開する
I can say oh I really wish that software
私はああ言うことができます私は本当にそのソフトウェアを望む
would do this this and this so I can sit
これ とこれを行うので私は座ることができます
in my computer and I can make it do this
私のコンピューターで 、 私は それを行う ことができ ます
this and this and then I submit it
これと これ そして それから私はそれを提出 する
what's called a pull request to your
プルリクエストと呼ばれるもの
code right so now you can absorb that
すぐにコードを書くことができるようになりました
change into your own software and that's
あなた自身のソフトウェアに変更してください。
what makes it great it's a it's a
それはそれが素晴らしいです何がそれはそれです
community it's a cloud platform that
コミュニティはクラウドプラットフォームです
allows developers to help each other
開発者が互いに助け合えるようにする
better open source right I guess yeah so
私は ええそう 思い 、より良いオープンソースの 権利
are they trying to shift then well I
彼らはそれから うまく シフトしようとしてい ますか
don't know we don't know yet what are
我々 はまだわからないかわかりません
they trying to do obviously now they own
彼らは 今 明らかにやろうとし ている
like the place leanness Torvalds from
Torvaldsが 寄りかかっている場所のように
Linux the developer who created the
Linuxの作成した開発者
Linux kernel develops it and publishes
Linuxカーネルがそれを開発し公開しています
via github so you know should we watch
github経由であなたは私たちが 見る べきであることを知っている ので
his channel
彼のチャンネル
watch his page and see if he changes his
彼のページを見て、彼が自分のページを変更したかどうかを確認してください
mind maybe he would say you know because
心 多分彼はあなたが知っているためだと思います
I imagine he's watching this very
私は彼がこれを見ているのを想像しています
closely and he's gonna say ok well let's
密接に彼はつもり OKも してみましょう と言っています
let's see let's back up he's now putting
見てみましょう彼が今置いているバックアップしましょう
his entire system in Microsoft hands
マイクロソフトの手の中の彼のシステム全体
essentially yeah but with that comes
基本的に ええ それが 来る と
their capability of aggregating all the
すべてを集約する能力
code of the universe that is on github
github 上にある宇宙のコード
ok that was gonna be my next point is
私の 次のポイントに なるつもりだった大丈夫 です
you are now handing over and the fact
あなたは今引き渡していると事実
that he's reporting to the cloud I mean
彼がクラウドに報告しているということです
it's not like it's just a server
単なるサーバーではない
somewhere I mean Microsoft is gonna
どこかに私はマイクロソフトが行くつもりだ
access this from all over just like sure
確かに 世界中からこれにアクセスする
can't we get up but there are they going
私たちは起きることはできませんが、彼らは行っています
to somewhere in there user agreement
そこにどこかにユーザー契約
have some sort of weirdly worded legal
ある種の奇妙な言葉を使った合法
thing that basically says you're giving
基本的に言っている こと
this to us to host for you therefore we
あなたのため にホストする ために私たちにこれを
own it right or we are it's licensed
それを正しく所有しているか、私たち は それがライセンスされているか
under GPL under various open-source
GPLの下で様々な オープンソースの 下で
licenses ok that may be the case but if
ライセンスは問題ないかもしれませんが
you have some amazing block of code
あなたはいくつかの素晴らしいコードブロックを持っています
within your program yeah who's to say
プログラム内ええ、誰が 言う ことです
that Microsoft with their new AI that
そのMicrosoftは彼らの新しいAIと
they're working on isn't gonna go oh
彼らは取り組んでいますああ行くつもりはないです
that's great code we're gonna take that
それは、 私たちが いることを 取るつもりだ偉大なコードです
component put it into our Microsoft
コンポーネントは私たちのマイクロソフトにそれを入れて
software and you don't get a penny but
ソフトウェアとあなたはペニーを得ることはありませんが
don't they have the right to do that
彼らにはそれをする権利がありませんか
anyways I guess but I mean it but if
とにかく 私は思いますが私はそれを意味します
they
彼ら
on the platform does that not add some
プラットフォーム上でいくつか追加されていません
more but them owning the platform does
より多くの、しかし彼らはプラットフォームを所有しています
not mean that they own the code they
コードを所有しているわけではありません。
can't make it their own and say it's
それを自分のものにすることはできず、それを言うことはできません
ours now no because if it's licensed
今、それがライセンスを受けています がない ので、場合我々
under GPL now the product that they've
GPLの下で今彼らが持っている製品
absorbed it into has to in turn be
それを吸収して
licensed under GPL that's the agreement
GPLの下でライセンス契約
behind that license
そのライセンスの後ろに
I still wonder if there's going to be
私はまだ不思議に思うだろう
some legal loophole because you're
あなたがいるので、いくつかの法的抜け穴
hosting it on their server I don't know
私は知らない 彼らのサーバーでそれをホスティング
time will tell Jeff time will tell and
時間はジェフに伝える時間はジェフに伝える
they're skeptical but you mention AI and
彼らは懐疑的ですが、あなたは AI について言及します
I think about the aggregation of the
の集約について考える
code and we think about the fact that
コードと私たちはその事実について考える
the CEO of their AI division is now
AI 部門の CEO は今
becoming the head of this so hey maybe
これの頭になるのでちょっと多分
there's something in that that's true
それは本当 だ ということで何かがあります
mm-hmm the FBI is invite is advising
FBIが招待しているmm-hmmがアドバイスしています
users of consumer grade routers and
消費者向けルーターのユーザー
network attached storage devices to
ネットワーク接続ストレージデバイス
reboot them as soon as possible to
できるだけ早くにそれらを再起動します
counter Russian engineered malware that
ロシアが設計したマルウェア
has infected hundreds and thousands of
何百、何千もの感染者
thousands of devices researchers from
からの何千ものデバイス研究者
Cisco's talo security team first
シスコのtaloセキュリティチームが最初
disclosed the existence of the malware
マルウェアの存在を開示
last month the detailed report said that
先月の詳細報告によると、
the malware infected more than 500,000
この マルウェア は 50万人 以上に感染しました
devices made by Linksys mikrotik night
Linksys によって製造されたデバイス mikrotik night
Netgear QNAP and tp-link known as VPN
VPNとして 知ら れている Netgear QNAPおよびTPリンク
filter filter the malware allowed
許可されたマルウェアをフィルタ処理する
attackers malware allowed tackers to
攻撃者のマルウェアがタッカーに許可する
collect communications launched launch
発売を 開始した通信を集めます
attacks on others and permanently
他人への攻撃と恒久的な攻撃
destroy the devices with a single
シングルでデバイスを破壊する
command the report said that the malware
レポートは、マルウェアが言った
was developed by trackers working for an
トラッカーによって開発されました
advanced nation possibly Russia and
先進国、 おそらく ロシア と
advised users of affected router models
影響を受けるルータモデルのユーザーへのアドバイス
to perform a factory reset or at minimum
工場出荷時の状態にリセットするか、 最低 で もします
to reboot the US Department of Homeland
米国国土省を再起動する方法
Security has also issued a statement
セキュリティ も声明を発表しました
advising that also home outter owners
その外出先の所有者に もアドバイス
power cycle or reboot their devices to
電源を入れ直すか、デバイスを再起動して
temporarily disrupt the malware
マルウェアを一時的に破壊する
as noted in the statements rebooting
再起動ステートメントに記載 され て いるように
serves the objective of first
最初の目的を果たします
temporarily preventing of infected
感染の一時的な防止
devices from running the stages that
そのステージを実行していないデバイス
collect data and other advanced attacks
データ収集およびその他の高度な攻撃
and secondly helping FBI officials to
第二に、FBI関係者が
track who was infected the statement
誰がそのステートメントに感染したのかを追跡する
said that the FBI is working with the
FBIが 作業し ていると述べました
nonprofit shadow foundation to
非営利のシャドーファンデーション
disseminate the IP addresses of the
のIPアドレスを広める
infected devices to ISPs and foreign
ISPや外国人に感染したデバイス
authorizations to notify end-users
エンドユーザーに通知する権限
authorities and researchers still don't
当局や研究者はまだしていない
know for certain how compromised devices
デバイスがどの程度侵害されたかを確実に知る
are initially infected they suspect that
最初に感染している
the attackers exploited known
悪用された攻撃者は既知のもの
vulnerabilities and default passwords
脆弱性とデフォルトのパスワード
that users had yet to patch or change
ユーザーがまだ パッチを適用または変更し ていない こと
the advice to reboot update changed
アップデートを再起動するためのアドバイスが 変更されました
default passwords and disable remote
デフォルトのパスワードとリモートの無効化
administration is sound and in most
管理は健全で、ほとんどの場合
cases requires no more than 15 minutes
場合は15分以内に必要
of course a more effective measure is to
もちろん より効果的な対策は
follow the advice cisco gave user gave
ciscoがユーザーから寄せられたアドバイスに従ってください
to users of effective effective devices
効果的な効果的な装置のユーザーへ
and perform a full factory reset which
フルファクトリリセット を 実行します 。
will permanently remove all of the
永久にすべてを削除します
malware including the first stage of the
の最初の段階を 含むマルウェア
malware thanks i feel like this story
マルウェアのおかげで私はこの物語のように感じます
happens often this is a particularly
頻繁に起こるこれは特にです
large one in that a lot of manufacturers
製造業者の多くの中で大きなもの
devices are affected right I mean it
デバイスは、 私はそれを意味する権利に影響を与えています
don't know a whole lot about the the
インクルード についての全体の多くを知りません
cause like what's the root underlying
根底にあるもののような原因
cause here and so they can say passwords
ここで引き起こすので、彼らはパスワードを言うことができます
and remote administration built into the
とリモート管理
devices so is it that somebody's written
デバイスなので、誰かが 書いたものです
a really good bot maybe using machine
多分マシンを使用して 、本当に良いボット
learning for example and attacking many
例を学び、 多く を攻撃 する
different routers and detecting oh this
別のルータとああこれを検出
one's a Netgear that I'm attacking right
自分が攻撃し ているネットギアだ
now so let's iterate through all the
それでは、すべてのものを繰り返してみましょう。
default passwords for Netgear devices oh
Netgearデバイス 用のデフォルトパスワード
look they've got remote administration
彼らはリモート 管理を持っているように見える
turned on on the router boom I'm in boom
私は ブーム になって います。
I'm Vince I've installed my malware
私は私のマルウェアをインストールしたことがあります
right and we don't know yet who who
正しいそして私たちはまだ誰が誰なのかわからない
started this and what they're accusing
これを始め、彼らが何を非難しているのか
Russia they are but I hate to think that
ロシア彼らはありますが、 私 はそれを考えるのが嫌いです
they would ever do something like that
彼らは その ような こと をするだろう
without knowing that there's some tie to
に 結びつきがある ことを 知ら ず に
Russia or any other culture
ロシアその他の 文化
so there must be some kind of evidence
だから何らかの証拠がなければならない
geolocation or something there must be
地理位置情報などがあるはずです
not one thing but yeah I I wonder okay
1つのことではありませんがええIIうん
so if you reboot your router that's
ルータを再起動すれば
great or you just our cycling looked at
素晴らしいか、サイクリングを見た
last week where Internet comes down
インターネット がやってくる 先週
restart the router exactly but in this
ルーターを正確に再起動する
particular case without this news story
この ニュース記事が ない特別な場合
coming out I wouldn't know that my
私は 私のことを 知らないだろう出てきます
router would need to be rebooted or
ルータが再起動する必要があるでしょうか
anything should I just be on a schedule
私はちょうどスケジュール通りにすべきです何でも
of doing that or what yeah just factory
それをすることの、 あるいは何のためにただ工場
reset every once in a while what can I
しばらくごとにリセット何私がすることができます
do like I feel like how would you know
私は あなた が どのように 知って いるような気が する
your router had malware yeah I think
ルーターは、マルウェアええ、私は 考えていました
that's a weird one because and I think
それは奇妙なことだと私は思います
sometimes it comes down to to not
時にはそれはしないようになる
necessarily just using the devices that
そのデバイスを使う
are provided by your ISP because they're
ISPから提供されています。
usually the most susceptible they're
通常最も影響を受けやすいのは
getting the bottom dollar on the most
最も上の一番下のドルを取得
amount of devices that they can buy for
購入可能な デバイス数
cheap so that they can install them on
彼らはそれらをインストールできるように安い
and all their sites and they're not
そしてすべての彼らの場所そしてそれらはない
always the most secure devices and
常に最も安全なデバイス と
they're not always patched and
彼らはいつもパッチを当てているわけではありません
up-to-date and everything else and they
最新のものと他のすべてのもの
have default passwords and by default we
デフォルトのパスワードが あり、 デフォルトで は
don't tend to hey ISP came in set up our
ちょっとISPが 私たちのセットアップ に来て する傾向がありません
Wi-Fi and we use the password they gave
Wi-Fiと私たちは彼らが与えたパスワードを使います
us well I mean how many people when they
私たちは彼らが 何 人いる か
get it from their ISP there's a sticker
彼らのISPからそれを得るステッカーがあります
on the back yeah sure that says this is
背中にそうしてください、これがあると言うこと
your password and then the technician
あなたのパスワード 、 それから 技術者
writes it on there you change you can
それをそこに書きます
change it yeah yeah but I think it
それを変えるええええ しかし私はそれを考える
predominantly has to do with not
主にないと関係がある
necessarily the Wi-Fi passwords so much
必ずしもWi-Fiパスワードはそんなに
as because then someone's got to be
それから、誰かがする必要があるように
sitting in the car within two kilometers
2キロ以内に車の中で 座って いる
of your house in order to do it
それをするためにあなたの家の
which is still an access its remote
それはまだ リモート アクセスです
access through the internet because
インターネットからのアクセス
remember this device is connected to the
この機器は
WAM the internet yeah and if it has a
インターネットをWAMはい 、それがあれば
default login password that you would
デフォルトのログインパスワード
use you ask the question can you change
あなたが質問をするのを変えるあなたは使うことができます
your Wi-Fi password yes you can by
あなたのWi-Fi パスワードはい
logging into your router going to the
ルータにログインして
wireless setup and changing your
ワイヤレス設定と変更
password and what if you didn't change
パスワードと変更しなかった場合
the password to login to your router
ルーター に ログインする ためのパスワード
that's the problem a lot of times it's
それは多くの時間が それだ問題です
like admin password so if that's what it
管理者パスワードが好きなのでそれがそれである場合
is and somebody somebody's bought has
誰かが買った人 と
found my router and can get into my
私のルータを発見し、 私に 取得することができます
router with admin password then they
管理者パスワードを持つルータ、 そして彼らは
have access to my network so I said you
私のネットワークにアクセスできるので、私はあなたに言った
know maybe don't just trust and I said
私は言った
just like don't just fall back on this
ちょうどこれに 頼らないように
device that the ISP gives you maybe we
ISPから提供されたデバイス
need to supplement with an internal
内部を補う必要がある
firewall that's between my network and
私のネットワークと
the Internet that's in addition to what
何 に加えてのインターネット
the ISP is giving me right and that
ISPが私に権利を与えている
would help protect because here's the
ここにあるので保護するのに役立ちます
fierce Asha as soon as someone can get
誰かが得ることができるとすぐ激しいアシャ
into that router a lot of them are
そのルータにそれらの多くはあります
powered by Linux for example yes they
彼らはイエス例えばLinuxが電力を供給します
may be able to open up SSH connections
SSH接続 を 開くことができるかもしれません
so that they can now connect into it and
彼らは今それに接続できる ように
access any of the computers on my
私のコンピュータにアクセスする
network if it's not Linux based if it's
Linuxベースでない場合はネットワーク
not SSH compatible or have that
SSHに対応していない
capability they can easily get in and
彼らが容易に 入る ことができる能力
open ports in my network port forwarding
ネットワークポートフォワーディングでポートを開く
and they can set up for example they can
そして彼らは 例えば彼らができるように セットアップする ことができます
see every computer's IP address on my
私のすべてのコンピュータのIPアドレスを見る
network because it those IP addresses
それはそれらのIPアドレスだからネットワーク
are being dished out by the router right
ルーターの右側から消えている
if I had a supplemental device that was
補助装置があれば
dishing out those IP addresses the
これらのIPアドレスは、ディッシング
router would never know what they are
ルーターは彼らが何であるかを決して知りません
that's great that's where it would help
それはそれが役立つだろうところです 素晴らしいです
so if they can see all the IP addresses
だから彼ら はすべてのIP アドレスを 見る ことができる場合
on my network so they see your desktop
私のネットワーク上であなたのデスクトップが見えるように
computer your laptop your phone they're
彼らのコンピューターあなたのラップトップあなたの携帯電話
gonna look at that desktop computer and
そのデスクトップコンピュータを見て
figure hey most likely that's Windows so
図ねえほとんど の場合はWindowsだ
let's open port 3389 - just to test
テストするために ポート3389を開きましょう
let's see if Samba is open and turned on
Sambaが開いていてオンになっている かどうか見てみましょう
like file sharing if networks file
networks ファイルの 場合はファイル共有と同様
sharing is connected and turned on so
共有が接続されていてオンになっている
that you can access your files on your
自分のファイルに アクセスできること
desktop from your laptop well they can
よく あなたのラップトップからデスクトップ
now open that up to their own computer
今すぐ自分のコンピュータにそれを開く
they can access your hard drive and
彼らはあなたのハードドライブにアクセスすることができます
guess what your C Drive has shared under
あなたのC ドライブ が共有している ものを推測
a hidden share and they've got full
隠された共有と彼らはいっぱいになりました
access to your computer so there's a lot
お使いのコンピュータ へのアクセスはとてもたくさんあります
of fear there with what they can be
彼らがいることができるものでそこに恐怖の
capable of by compromising that one
それを妥協することによって可能
device so we can reset it to knock them
我々は それらをノックする ためにそれをリセットすることができますので、デバイス
off of it if they're on we can factory
それらがオンになっている場合はオフにします
reset it to remove what they've done but
リセットして、 行っ たことを削除 します
then we've got to reset up everything if
それから私達はすべてをリセットしなければならない
you do that please don't reuse the same
あなたは同じことを再利用しないでください
passwords yeah we can wipe it all and do
パスワードうん 私たちはそれを すべて 拭いて 行う ことができ ます
all that and then supplement with a good
それがすべてで 、 それから 善を補う
firewall and maybe that's the best way
ファイアウォールとおそらくそれが最善の方法です
to do it
それを行うには
thank you it's still scary nonetheless
それでもなお 怖いです
it can be if you have questions if
質問がある場合は
you're not sure anything that I just
あなたは私のことだけで はわからない
said please send them in go to our
私たち に 行って それら を 送って ください
website category 5 TV make sure when you
ウェブサイトのカテゴリ 5テレビを 確認してくださいときに
go to contact us that you select that
あなたがそれを選択したことを私達に連絡するために行きなさい
you are sending in a question for the
あなたに 質問を送り ます
show otherwise it may go to the wrong
そうでなければそれは間違って行くかもしれない
inbox and never get answered so make
受信箱に入っても返事が ないので作成する
sure you're selecting but it's to go to
必ずあなたが選択しているが、それはに行きます
the show Apple on Monday previewed a
ショーアップルは月曜日にプレビューしました
variety of security and privacy features
さまざまなセキュリティおよびプライバシー機能
it plans to add to Mac OS and iOS
Mac OS とiOS に追加する予定です
operating systems including encrypted
暗号化を含むオペレーティングシステム
FaceTime group calls password management
FaceTimeグループはパスワード管理を呼びます
tools and camera and microphone
ツールとカメラとマイク
protections apple also released a beta
保護アップルはまたベータ版をリリース
version of the upcoming iOS 12 that
今後の iOS 12のバージョン
apparently kills off two iphone
どうやら2 iPhoneを殺す
unlocking tools used by law enforcement
法執行機関が使用するロック解除ツール
around the world to access phones
電話にアクセスするために世界中で
without knowing the unlock code the
ロック解除 コードを知らなくて も
feature known as USB restricted mode
USB制限モードと呼ばれる機能
requires that users unlock their iPhone
ユーザーは 自分の iPhoneの ロックを解除する必要があります
with a password when connecting to it to
に接続 する ときにパスワードを入力する
a USB device it requires a password each
USBデバイスの場合はそれぞれパスワードが必要です
time a phone that hasn't been unlocked
ロック解除されていない 電話の時間
in the past hour tries to connect to a
過去1時間でに接続しようとしました
device using a lightning connection the
雷接続を使用する装置
password requirements tart largely
パスワードの要件は、主にタルト
neutralizes iphone unlocking tools
iPhoneの ロック解除ツールを 無効にし ます
provided by companies called cellebrite
cellebrite という 会社によって提供さ れてい ます
and grey shift which use USB
とUSBを使用したグレーシフト
connectivity to bypass iOS restrictions
iOSの制限を回避するための接続性
on the number of incorrect pin guesses
不正確なピン推測の 数について
that can be entered into an iPhone with
それはと iPhoneに 入力 する ことができます
those limitations removed police can
これらの制限を取り除くことで警察はできる
make an unlimited number of pin guesses
ピン推測を無制限にする
when attempting to unlock a confiscated
没収さ れたものを 開錠 しようと した とき
iPhone often aided by robotic
iPhoneはしばしばロボットによって支援される
unlocking system previously iOS betas
システムのロックを解除する以前のiOSのベータ版
had USB restrictions that required the
必要なUSBの制限がありました
entering of a password when it hadn't
パスワードが入力されていないときにパスワードを入力する
been unlocked for seven days those us be
七日のためにロック解除されたもの たちはなります
restricted modes were later removed
制限モードは後で削除されました
before Apple issued final versions of
Appleがの 最終版を 発行する前 に
the iOS the restrictions this time
今回のiOSの制限
around are much more stringent because
周りははるかに厳しいので
police would have no more than 60
警察は60 人以下になるだろう
minutes between the time that they
その時間間隔
obtain an iPhone and connect it to an
iPhoneを入手して
unlocking tool we should remember that
私たちが覚えておくべきロック解除ツール
though though at
でも
Apple has previously removed USB
Appleは以前にUSBを 削除しました
restricted mode before releasing final
ファイナルをリリースする前の制限モード
versions and may do so again with iOS 12
バージョンとiOS 12で再びそうするかもしれない
the new beta also features end-to-end
新しいベータ版も エンドツーエンドの機能を備えています
encryption built-in password management
暗号化内蔵パスワード管理
and several privacy enhancements so
そしていくつかのプライバシー強化
sounds great let's switch to Apple well
アップル ウェル に大きなLETのスイッチを鳴らし
how do I get that but without having to
どのように私はそれを得るのですが、 し なくても、
get Apple like how can I get that
どのように 私は それ を得る こと ができますようにアップル を入手
without an iPhone good question
iPhoneのいい質問なしで
chatroom this is one for you folks if
チャットルームこれは あなたの ためのもの です
you can I well I've never heard of that
私はそのことを聞いたことがない
USB locking mechanism in an Android
AndroidのUSBロック機構
phone okay heard of that that doesn't
電話は 大丈夫ということを聞いた
mean it doesn't exist
存在しないという意味
I want a pretty phone like I'm not a
私はではないような私はきれいな携帯電話が欲しい
phone guy I want my private room yeah I
電話の男は、 私はそう 私の個室が欲しいです
think that's a great idea because this
これ は素晴らしい アイデア だと思います
is one of the things is that there
物事の一つはそこにあるということです
unlock they're making it so that the
ロックを解除して
because you know you guess the password
あなた はパスワードを推測している ことを 知っている ので
ten times and all of a sudden of locks
10回そして 突然のロック
you only kind of think but if they're
あなただけ の 種類 のだと思うが、彼らはしている場合
using a tool over USB it makes sense
USB経由でツールを使用することは理にかなっています
that hey if we disable the USB
USBを無効にしたら、ちょっと
connection until you enter the password
パスワードを入力するまで接続
now they can't do that I like it I like
今、彼らは私が 私が好きなことを 好きなことを行うことはできません
that feature a lot I want it I just
その機能 私は それだけで私たい 多くのことを
don't want an iPhone I know no there's
iPhoneを望んでいない 私は何があるのを知っていません
like a software that's been developed
開発され たソフトウェアのように
that you can download through you know
あなたが 知ってダウンロードすること が できます
in an Android store or something well
Androidストアなどで
you know what I I don't know that it
あなたはIIがそれを知らないのか知っている
would be supplemental it's gonna be a
それは補足になるだろう
core OS feature right but I could
コアOSの機能は正しいのですが
imagine that if it doesn't exist in
想像し 、それが 存在し ない場合 に
Android it wasn't you know yeah the the
Androidそれはあなた がそうだね
the idea behind it is is non-proprietary
その背後にある考え方は非専有的です
I mean you can't
できないということです
how can you patent something like that
どのようにあなたはそのような何かを特許取得することができます
right so yeah that's true I'm sure that
右そうそう それが本当私は確信しています
someone will make something similar on
誰かが似たようなものを作るだろう
Android part of the Android OS but will
Android OSの Android 部分ですが
it be you know what if your phone can't
あなたの携帯電話ができない場合、それはあなたが何を知っていますか
be updated to version 9 of Android right
Androidの バージョン9 に更新される権利
exam out well I mean and that will be
よく試験をすることを意味し、 それはなります
part of it is that it won't be entirely
それの一部はそれが 完全ではないということです
backwards compatible but like I haven't
後方互換性がありますが、私はしていません
I have a samsung phone mm-hmm and there
私はサムスンの携帯電話mm-hmmを持っています
is the Samsung App Store device that
Samsung App Storeの端末は
comes with my phone so I can see Samsung
私 は サムスン を見ることができるように 私の携帯電話が付属してい ます
themselves
彼ら自身
developing an app that becomes part of
の一部となるアプリを開発する
the okay turtle that goes hey do you
やあ行くいいカメ
want this you can download it and then
これが欲しいならあなたはそれをダウンロードしてそれから
that's part of the core of your phone
それはあなたの携帯電話のコアの一部です
whoo why are you no different than if
誰がなぜあなたは変わらないのですか
you had you know like an algae or
あなたは 藻のように知っ ていた か
something that they could maybe develop
彼らが開発するかもしれない何か
their own version of it that you could
あなたができるそれの彼ら自身のバージョン
download from okay you know I could see
大丈夫からダウンロードあなたは私が見ることができた知っている
something like that happening the foo
そのような ことがfooで起こっている
has a phone that uses NFC and a UB key
NFCと UBキーを 使用して携帯電話を持っています
in order to to enforce two-factor
二要素 を強制 するため に
authentication okay and I just wonder
認証大丈夫と私は 疑問に思います
the foo if if that would prevent the
もしそれが妨げになるならばfoo
capability of plugging in a USB cable
USBケーブルを差し込む機能
and adding these backdoor patches that
これらのバックドアパッチを追加して
remove those restrictions like could it
それができるようにそれらの制限を取り除く
could I don't know what the government
政府が何なのかわからない
has as far as capabilities know and so
能力が 知る 限りで は
[Laughter]
[笑い]
factor authentication is a good idea I
因子認証は良い考えです
think also that simply you know for
単にあなたが 知って いるとも思う
myself like I don't keep anything
私は何もしないのが好き
private on my phone no I would just have
自分の携帯電話上のプライベートがない私は持っているでしょう
to change my google it just account i
私の グーグルを 変更するには 、それはちょうど 私の アカウント
password and things you just feel like
パスワードとあなただけのよう に感じるもの
you want your stuff to stay private
あなたのものをプライベートにしておきたい
though like the things you've chosen to
あなたが選んだもののように
be private she want them to stay private
彼女は彼らがプライベート滞在したい プライベートで
you know so if I'm giving my phone over
私は私の電話を渡しているなら あなたは そう 知っ てい ます
say at the border say they'd do a thing
国境で言う彼らは物事をやると言う
where they just want to check your phone
彼らはただ あなたの電話 を チェックし たいところ
at the order I I don't want them to
順序IIでそれらがしたくない
you're a person now a national security
あなたは今国家安全保障の人です
threat
脅威
I hear Canada yep really yep yeah two
私はカナダ うん本当にうんうん2
weeks ago really a much better story
数週間前、本当にずっと良い話
just for the record we are benign we're
ちょうど記録のために私達 は 私達 が良性である
so please forgive us for anything we
だから私たちに何か を許してください
have done because that's the Canadian
それはカナダだ から行っています
way we're so sorry sorry
ごめんなさい
a CSIS staged its annual Computex
CSISが年次 Computexを 上演しました
keynote and shown off laptops with dual
基調講演とラップトップをデュアルで見せた
screens but it's not at all what you're
画面が、それはあなたがまったく何もない
imagining the Zenbook pro 15 is a 15
Zenbook pro 15を 想像 すると15
inch notebook packin up to a hex core
六角コア までインチノートブックpackin
core I 9 with 16 gigs of RAM GTX 1050 TI
16ギグのRAM GTX 1050 TI を搭載したコアI 9
graphics and a one terabyte solid-state
グラフィックスと1テラバイトのソリッドステート
drive
ドライブ
I know it has a main 15.6 inch screen
私はそれがメインの15.6インチスクリーンを持っているのを知っています
capable of 4k Ultra HD and it has a
4KウルトラHDが可能で、それは持っています
second screen which is different from
とは異なるセカンドスクリーン
anything we've ever seen
今まで見たことのあるもの
it's a Full HD multi-touch screen in
それはフルHDマルチタッチスクリーンです。
place of the laptops usual touchpad Asus
通常のタッチパッド Asus のノートパソコンの場所
has called this the screen pad and has
これをスクリーンパッドと呼び、
designed apps including a calculator and
計算機を含む設計されたアプリ
custom controls for Microsoft Office and
Microsoft Office用のカスタムコントロール
YouTube to run in it the laptop goes on
ラップトップが 動作する YouTube
sale next month for $2,300 us oh I love
来月の売り上げは2,300ドル。
the idea AHA I really like it I love
AHA私はそれが大好きです
where this world is going when do I get
この世界 が どこに向かっているのか
one think of this right
この権利について考える人
come on manufacturers this should have
これがあるべき製造元に来る
been around forever this is smart it's
永遠の周りされて、これは スマートなそれのあります
it's a beautiful idea but however this
それは美しい考えですが、しかしこれは
is Jeff but no but how many times do
はジェフですが、何 回やっていますか
people go I drop my laptop like so you
人々 は 私 が そうあなたの ように私のラップトップ を 落とす
get it no no but now an otterbox doesn't
いいえ、しかし今ではOtterboxはそうではありません
get for a laptop really maybe okay like
以下のような、本当に多分大丈夫ラップトップのために得ます
if I was to drop this don't it's mine I
私がこれを落とすことになっていたのなら、私のものではない
know but if I was to drop it chances are
知っていますが、私がそれを落とすことになっていたならばチャンスはあります
I'm not gonna be damaging the keyboard
私はキーボードを傷つけるつもりはないよ
but now if you've got a screen and you
しかし今あなたがスクリーンを 持っていてあなたが
have a glass plane that is your keyboard
あなたのキーボードであるガラス飛行機を持っています
you drop that sucker you've doubled the
あなたはその吸盤を落とし たが
chances I feel like for the
私はのように感じるチャンス
accident-prone not a smart purchase okay
事故を起こしやすいスマートではない購入
raining on this parade for the record
記録のため に このパレードで 雨が降る
mr. butterfingers over here
氏。バターフィンガー
PSA don't drop your laptop especially if
PSAは、 特に 場合は 、あなたのラップトップをドロップしません
it's $2,300 I really want to just get my
それは私が本当に私のものを手に入れたいだけの2,300ドルです
hands on it and like I want to see what
その 上 、私は何を見てみたいような 手
it feels like I feel like I'll feel like
私はのように感じるでしょうよう に感じるようにそれは感じています
I'm in like Minority Report or something
マイノリティレポートみたいなものか
I don't know I think to me it reminds me
私には 思い出さない
of what I thought the switch should have
私はスイッチが持っているべきだと思ったものの
been like with the touchscreen and
タッチスクリーン と同じようにされていると
everything interacting with the TA and
TAと 相互作用するすべてのもの
maybe it is for some games but but I
多分それはいくつかのゲームのためですが、私は
like that idea that it's got hot keys my
それは私のホットキーを持っているという考えのように
Wacom tablet for for drawing which I'm
私が描くことのためのワコムタブレット
not an artist but my daughter is has a
アーティストではありませんが、私の娘は
lot of hot keys and stuff around that
たくさんのホットキーと その 周りの もの
you talk
あなたは話します
with the pen and it does certain actions
ペンで、それは特定のアクションを行います
and things and I love the fact that this
そして物事と私はこれが事実であることが大好き
touchpad now becomes an action center
タッチパッドが アクションセンターに なりました
that can be you know maybe app
それはあなたが多分アプリを知っていることができます
developers can create apps that will
開発者は、
supplement your application now as
今すぐあなたのアプリケーションを補完する
somebody who codes all the time how
いつもコーディングしている人
would that change in physical dexterity
その 器用さの 変化
impact the way that you type because I
私がいるのであなたがタイプ する方法に影響を与える
mean I'm sure you could be looking at
私はあなたが見ていると確信しています
your screen and just say it what if you
あなたのスクリーン とちょうど あなたが そうなら何でも それを言う
have your hand scanned on it and then it
あなたの手がそれをスキャンし、それからそれを持っている
automatically mised you guys know
自動的にあなたがみんなを知って逃した
nothing about this no it has a real
この こと については何もない
physical keyboard just like your normal
通常の物理キーボード
laptop but your touch pad the touch pad
ノートパソコン が、あなたの タッチパッド タッチパッド
that you use your mouse has been
マウスを使っている
replaced with a touchscreen okay then I
大丈夫私はその後 、 タッチスクリーンに 置き換え
misunderstood the news story I thought I
私が思ったニュース記事を誤解した
was talking about I thought it's a whole
私はそれが全体だと思った
keyboard no we're talking the touch pad
キーボードいいえ私たちは タッチパッドを 話している
is a multi-touch touchscreen I know it's
私が知っているマルチタッチタッチスクリーンです
hard to understand she has bad vision
理解が難しい彼女は視力が悪い
don't make fun of her it's because the
彼女をからかわないでください。
letters were white and shredding them
手紙は白くてそれらを細断した
green now does it make sense it does I'm
緑は今では意味があるの ですか
picturing like two planes of glass big
大きな2枚のガラスのように描く
touchscreen cuz it's gonna have a
それは持っているつもりだタッチスクリーンのcuz
calculator it's good now do we get the
電卓、それは良いことだ、今私たちが 入手 できますか
news now do we understand what's cool I
ニュース今私たちは何が クールなの か理解していますか
think it's even better than what you
それはあなたよりもっと良いと思います
were thinking is what you were thinking
考えていたの はあなたが考えていたものです
thinking was nonsense no it made no
考えはナンセンスでした
sense
感覚
who would ever make that Jeff I just
誰がそのジェフを作ったことがありますか
thought it was neat I'm like that's cool
それはクールだように私はきちんとした考え
when Sasha said it is not like anything
サーシャがそれは何も好きではないと言ったとき
you've you're thinking she didn't mean
あなたは彼女が意味していないと思っているのよ
it that way
それはそのように
like that the presenter would completely
プレゼンターが完全に
not understand what it is that it is
それはそれがあることが何であるかを理解していませ
that they're making
彼らが作っていること
thanks to marsh man Roy W Nash and our
沼地の人Roy W Nashと私たちのおかげで
community of viewers for submitting
投稿者のコミュニティ
stories to us this week thanks for
今週のストーリー
watching the category-five TV newsroom
カテゴリ5テレビ ニュースルームを 見て
subscribe here for all your tech news
あなたの 技術ニュース をすべて購読する
with a slight linux - for more from the
ちょっとしたLinuxで - もっと
category 5 TV newsroom visit our website
category 5 TVニュースルーム当社のウェブサイトをご覧ください
category 5 dog TV thank you for watching
カテゴリ5犬のテレビ見ていただきありがとうございます
I'm Robbie Ferguson
私はロビーファーガソンです
I'm Sasha Rickman and I'm Jeff Weston
私はSasha Rickmanです、そして、私はJeff Westonです
thank you good night
おやすみなさい ありがとう
hey I hope you had fun did you have fun
こんにちは私はあなたが楽しんでいたと思います
I had fun it's always an adventure from
私は それが 常に 冒険である こと を楽しん で い ました
blurry vision to a teleprompter that
テレプロンプターに対するぼやけたビジョン
simply has a battery low indicator
単にバッテリー残量表示
fullscreen over top of the lens of our
私たちのレンズの上にフルスクリーン
camera we always get through yes exactly
私たちはいつも通り抜けるカメラ
and I hope that you've enjoyed yourself
そして 私は あなたがあなた自身を楽しんだこと を願って います
again this week Jeff finds away you have
今週もまた、 ジェフはあなたがいることに気づいた
a good time yeah I'm gonna put on my
良い時間うん私は私の上に置くつもりだ
face mask so that I can't see anything
何も 見えない ように フェイスマスク
these just meditate eyes yeah to answer
これらはただ答えるためにええ目を瞑想します
your question the foo tonight has been a
あなたの 質問 今夜 の foo はされています
longer show yes yes you'll pale the
長くはいはいあなたは 淡い ますを示して
paper have a great week everybody we'll
紙には素晴らしい週があります
see you next week bye
また来週さようなら
[Music]
[音楽]